Bernie Or Elizabeth Be Informed Compare Them On The Issue That Matter Issue Who Make The Dankest Meme,"['bernie sanders', 'elizabeth warren']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'MISC']","['Bernie', 'Elizabeth', 'Dankest']"
Extending The Brexit Deadline Until October 31St In Order To Ensure A Deal Everyone Can Agree With Using The Extension To Elect A New Prime Minister And Then Take A Recess Until One Month Before The Deadline Imgflip Com,['uk government'],['B-VIL'],['MISC'],['Brexit']
Kwai Gkwa 0964 Nnevvy Applause To Thai From Hong Kong Why Thai Did Not Get Hurt Cultural Difference Just Stay In The Wall,"['thais', 'hong kong']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Kwai Gkwa', 'Thai', 'Hong Kong', 'Thai']"
So I Order This Foce Mask To Protect Ogainst Fhe Corond Virus Hooold Up It Say Something Here Made In China,"['china', 'face mask', 'made in china', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG', 'LOC']","['Ogainst', 'Corond', 'China']"
Best Candidate For Ja 2020 Joe Biden Kamala Harris Bernie Sanders Tiktok Eliguthrie,"['joe biden', 'bernie sanders', 'kamala harris', 'tiktok']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER']","['Ja', 'Joe Biden', 'Kamala Harris', 'Bernie Sanders', 'Tiktok Eliguthrie']"
Breaking News El Ch And Mannequin Then He Bought Lingerie For News Awoman Who Wa Seen Outside The Store Wearing A Man Wearing A Donald Trump Mask Went Into A Victoria Secret Store Olged Female Customer Han A Meiania Trump Maskwho Waswaiting For Him To Come Out Sam We Have The Surveillance Imgfip Com Film At 11 Ron Burgundy Meme Imgflip Annel S Team,"['donald trump', '', 'victoria secret store', 'melania trump', 'victoria secrets']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'ORG']","['El Ch', 'Mannequin', 'Donald Trump', 'Victoria', 'Secret', 'Han A Meiania Trump', 'Ron', 'Burgundy', 'Annel S Team']"
Mask Trump Trump Den Ce Help Your Child Find The Right Halloween Costume,"['donald trump', 'barack obama', 'halloween']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Trump Trump Den Ce']
Hantavirus China Discovered New Virus Whole World Right Now,"['china', 'people', 'world', 'hantavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Hantavirus', 'China', 'World']"
When It S Finally 2020 But You Realize That Both 1820 And 1920 Had Massive Plague Outbreak In Regard To The Recent Virus Spreading From China,"['china', 'plague', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
Nese Newyear Chira S Attermpt At Controlling A Pandemi Wuhan Corona Virus,"['wuhan coronavirus', 'china', 'chinese new year', 'coronavirus', 'chinese']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Nese', 'Newyear', 'Chira', 'Pandemi Wuhan', 'Corona']"
Hantavirus Man Dy In 2020 Can T Get Any Worse China After Testing Positive To New Virus Coronavirus Coronavirus Hantavirus We Re Doing A Sequel,"['hanta virus', 'coronavirus', 'hantavirus', 'china']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Hantavirus', 'China', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus', 'Hantavirus']"
Dr Grayfang Orgrayfang Ha Tete Dryteng Ang Yay A Me Getting Food And Alcohol Delivered During Quarantine Enhhan G Do Bt Oa Rear A Ve Ha Ne He Oe Fe Ten D Laper Leave It On The Doornte And Get The Bell Out Of Here,"['dr grayfang', 'quarantine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Grayfang', 'Orgrayfang']"
Henh After Corona Swine Flu Bubonicplague Ha Been Detected In China We Re In The Endgame Now,"['bubonic plague', 'people', 'china', 'swine flu', 'corona swine flu', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Henh', 'Corona Swine', 'China']"
China Built A Wall And They Have Almost No Mexican Case In Point,"['donald trump', 'great wall of china', 'china', 'mexicans', 'wall']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Mexican']"
When S Finally 2020 But You Reakze That Boch 1820 And 1920 Had Massive Vew V S S May Be Ted Myte Ein Tha Plague Outbreoks China Ha Begun Killing The Karen,"['china', 'karens', 'plague', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Karen']"
Play It A Safe Don T Worry Leave Our Border En Shut Our Border To China Now 98 Leave Them Open Close Them Now This Pal Ha Ended 33 K Vates,['china'],['B-VIL'],['LOC'],['China']
Reporter Why Are You Calling It The Chinese Virus Trump Because It Came From China Reporter Don T You Think Thats A Little Racist Tho Trump Oit Came From Chi Na,"['donald trump', 'china', 'reporter', 'coronavirus', 'chinese virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Chinese Virus', 'Trump', 'China', 'Trump', 'Chi Na']"
Actual Footage Of Jared Leto Returning From His 12 Day Meditation Retreat And Learning About Coronavirus Adan Tore Ca The P Lhed Etend En,"['jared leto', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Jared Leto', 'Coronavirus', 'P']"
When The Chinese Student Start Coughing Time Ha Come Hmm,"['chinese student', 'coughing chinese student', 'chinese students']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chinese']
Internet Explorer Internetexp Breaking News 2 Reported Case Of A New Virus In China 03 11 Pm 18 Mar 20 42 Like,"['internet explorer', 'china', 'breaking news', 'coronavirus', 'new virus in china']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Internet Explorer Internetexp', 'China']"
Coronavirus Exist Everyone Oh It In China It Is Too Far Away To Get To Me Coronavirus A Month Later I Like To Move It Move It,"['coronavirus', 'china']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Coronavirus', 'China', 'Coronavirus']"
Coronavirus Safe Isolation Face Mask Glove,"['bikers', 'coronavirus', 'gloves', 'face mask', 'isolation']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
They Have Had U Cowering For Over Half A Century Ore Like 3 4 Century Good Lil Sheeple Ng Flip Com,[],[],['PER'],['Sheeple']
The Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'chinese', 'chinese coronavirus', 'kung flu']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu']
Government Stay Inside Half Of The U Population Catch Me Outside How Bow Dat Phil Starecat Com,"['us population', 'us government', 'government']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'PER', 'ORG']","['Bow Dat', 'Phil', 'Starecat', 'Com']"
Congratulatios You Have Won Martk Free Trip To China,"['china', 'trip to china']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Martk', 'China']"
Chelsea Clinton Chelseaclinton President Trump Ha Left The U S Dangerously Underprepared To Face A Public Health Crisis Like A Coronavirus Outbreak Devisridhar And I Explain How Via Cnn Lars Printz N Larsprintzen Feb 25 Replying To Pchelseaclinton Devisridhar And Cnn So Far More People In The U Have Died Trying To Testify Against You Mother Than Ha Died From Corona Virus,"['donald trump', 'chelsea clinton', 'lars printzen', 'cnn', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Chelsea Clinton', 'Chelseaclinton', 'Trump', 'U S', 'Coronavirus', 'Devisridhar', 'Lars Printz', 'Larsprintzen', 'Pchelseaclinton', 'Devisridhar', 'U', 'Corona']"
Covid Fact Per The Cdc Elfective 07 10 2020 U Population 329 934 000 Covid Case 3 106 931 Death 132 855 That Mean Only 0 4 Le Than 1 Of American Have Even Contracted The Virus It Also Mean 95 72 Of Those Survive Best Of All Only 0 04 Of American Have Dled From This Virus A 99 96 Survival Rate You Dan L See That Hese Mask And Reulriclions Are Not Polically Motivated A Ruse Defined 113 000 People Have Recovered From Coronavirus Try Sharing That Instead When Case Not Recovery Are Defined,"['politicians', 'coronavirus', 'covid facts', 'us population']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Covid', 'Covid', 'American', 'American', 'Coronavirus']"
Doe That Covid Bill Include 10 For The Big Guy,"['joe biden', 'hunter biden', 'covid19']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Doe That Covid', 'Guy']"
Fiction Need To Be Somewhat Realistic For People To Believe It Reality Is Under No Such Constraint Real Worker In China March 2020,"['china', 'workers']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
Mecessit Is The Mother Of Oll Invention Thefunnybeaver Com,"['funny mask', 'face mask', 'orange']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['Mecessit', 'Thefunnybeaver Com']"
All In Un Ana A M Ditry Before After Our Norwegian Poker Translator In Lockdown,['norwegian poker translator'],['B-VIC'],"['ORG', 'MISC']","['Ditry', 'Norwegian']"
Barack Obama Present A Medal To Himself For Creating Job During The Trump Administration,"['barack obama', 'donald trump']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL']","['PER', 'MISC']","['Barack Obama', 'Trump Administration']"
The 2 Type Of Communist,"['communist', 'china', 'russia']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Communist']
Official Just Confirmed China S Mystery Virus Spread By Human To Human Transmission The Guy Playing Plague Inc On The Area 51 Computer,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'area 51', 'virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'LOC']","['China', 'S', 'Mystery', 'Plague Inc', 'Area 51']"
New Swine Flu Like Virus With Human Pandemic Potential Found In China Whole World To China Aae Band Kar Band Kari,"['china', 'swine flu', 'new swine flu like virus', 'virus']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Swine Flu', 'China', 'China', 'Aae Band', 'Kar Band', 'Kari']"
This Is Hob He Voted For Trump This Is Bob S Friend Sally Sally Voted For Clinton Botre Satlyare Stilt Frienda Beenese Bob And Sallyare Both Adulte Bettke Botramt Sally,"['donald trump', 'bill clinton', 'hillary clinton', 'hillary clinton']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER']","['Hob', 'Trump', 'Bob', 'Sally', 'Clinton', 'Botre Satlyare', 'Beenese', 'Bob', 'Sallyare']"
What Do Donald Trump And A Pumpkin Have In Common They Re Orange On The Outside Hollow On The Inside And Should Be Tossed Out In Early November,"['donald trump', 'pumpkin']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Donald Trump', 'Pumpkin']"
Chance A Virus With A 99 97 Recovery Rate False Alter My Dna From An Experimental Vaccine With No Liabilty From A Corrupt Industry,"['dna', 'virus', 'experimental vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Re Photo If You Love American You Re Generally A Conservative If You Hate American You Re Usually A Liberal Cprione,"['conservative', 'liberal', 'charlie kirk', 'american', 'usa']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER']","['American', 'Conservative', 'American', 'Liberal', 'Cprione']"
Pfizer Peeple Working At Home In Sweatpants,"['pifzer', 'work from home', 'pfizer']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Pfizer Peeple']
Having A Bad Day Just Remember That Time Obama Lost It When He Saw A Baby Dressed A The Pope,"['barack obama', 'baby']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Obama']
Just Had The Covid 19 Vaccine Feeling Great Makeameme Org,"['covid vaccine', 'covid vaccine', 'covid vaccine']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Covid', 'Makeameme Org']"
Whole World Thinking Corona Virus Will Be End Soon Hantavirus,"['hanta virus', 'hantavirus', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['World Thinking', 'Corona Virus', 'Hantavirus']"
E Cw Newe Me Rce Corporate Need You To Find The Difference Between This Picture And This Picture They Re The Same Picture,"['mainstream media', 'china', 'media house', 'chinese communist party', 'media houses']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Me When I Get My Covid Vaccine Memezila Com,"['covid vaccine', 'covid vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Covid', 'Memezila Com']"
Hechevs The White Hc Washington Nik News Special Report Live White House Briefing From Coronavirus Task Force For Latest Update Go To Nbcnews Com Coronavirus,"['donald trump', 'dr  anthony fauci', 'white house', 'nbc news']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Hechevs', 'White Hc', 'Washington Nik News', 'White House', 'Coronavirus', 'Task Force', 'Nbcnews Com']"
Society Stayhome Homeless People,"['homeless people', 'society']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Society']
Just In Case You Are Wondering How Much The Medium Control People American Ha Been Vaccinating Cattle For Coronavirus For Year Yet The News Tell You It S New And Gunna Kill You All So Go Buy Mask 10 Dos 20 Ml Bovine Rotavirus Coronavirus Vaccine Klled Virus Escherichia Coli Bacterin For Veterinary Use Only,"['media', 'people', 'coronavirus vaccine', 'cattle', 'media house', 'coronavirus', 'mask', 'american', 'covid vaccine']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['American', 'Coronavirus', 'Bovine Rotavirus Coronavirus', 'Escherichia Coli']"
China Virus Can Be Contracted Only Through Human Contact Introvert,"['introverts', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
17H 0 Lighten Up Why Biden No Get Virus,"['kim jong un', 'kim jong un', 'coronavirus', 'joe biden', 'kim jong un', 'virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Biden']
In Casee Mnks E Otola Corona,"['corona beer', 'corona']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Casee', 'Mnks', 'Otola Corona']"
When It S Finally 2020 But You Realize That Both 1820 And 1920 Had Massive Plague Outbreak Hmm,['plague'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
China To Ban Online Gaming Chatting With Foreigner Outside Great Firewall Report Cor Psychopathic Idisc You Re Never Going To See Those Freaky Friend Of Yours Again Never,"['china', 'online gamers', 'firewall']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['China', 'Foreigner', 'Firewall', 'Cor Psychopathic Idisc']"
Coronavirus Testing Sc M Th Lars Interesting How The U Government Label Corona Virus Patient Consumer,"['us government', 'coronavirus patients', 'covid19 patients', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC']","['U Government', 'Corona']"
Stop Calling It The China Virus Spanish Flu,"['china virus', 'spanish flu', 'spanish people']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Calling It', 'China Virus', 'Spanish Flu']"
Funny How The Coronavirus Popped Up And Suddenly There No More Hong K Ng Protestors China China,"['china', 'hong kong protestors', 'hong kong', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'Hong K Ng', 'China', 'China']"
Me Serving My Kid Quarantine Pizza Made With Tortilla Eifeandtimesofmom Buongiorno,['quaratine food'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'MISC']","['Tortilla', 'Eifeandtimesofmom']"
Cat Meme Go Uiral I Coronavirus Outbreak The Coronavirus Pandemic Seethchina Mrni T,"['cat meme', 'pandemic', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Cat', 'I', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']"
If It Came From Wuhan In China Then How Is It Racist To Call Itthe China Wuhan Corona Virus,"['china', 'china wuhan coronavirus', 'coronavirus', 'wuhan']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan', 'China', 'China', 'Wuhan Corona Virus']"
Steve King 999 According To Cnn It Took Obama Mllions Infected And Over 1 000 Death To Declare The Hini Flu A Health Emergency Pointosa Under Presidenttrump Coronavirus Wa Declared A Health Emergency And Public Safety Measure Were In Place Before A Single U S Death O0Ccurred 260 Cermeres K Share,"['donald trump', 'barack obama', 'pandemic', 'cnn', 'coronavirus', 'h1n1', 'h1n1 flu']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Steve King', 'Obama', 'Hini Flu', 'U S']"
When You Ve Been Hiding A Zombie Bite And Can Feel Yourself Starting To Turn But You Don T Want To Tell Your Group De Wfauft,"['donald trump', 'zombie bite']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Also Dude China Virus Is Not The Preferred Nomenclature Covid19 Please,"['china', 'covid19', 'china virus']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['China Virus']
Obama Whisper Put The Laser Pointer Away Or Give It To Me Ml Docd,"['barack obama', 'joe biden']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC']","['Obama', 'Laser Pointer']"
The Corona Virus Spreading Through China Hong Kong Get A Longer Holiday,"['china', 'hong kong', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Corona Virus', 'China', 'Hong Kong']"
James Wood E Realjames 13 Aug V This Is Our Last Stand Folk And Here S Your Last Defender If They Take Him Down American Is Gone Forever Vote For Realdonald Trump Like Your Life Depends On It 24K 13 76 2K 174K,"['donald trump', 'james woods', 'james wood']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'PER']","['James Wood', 'American', 'Realdonald Trump']"
My Government Will Keep Me Safe From An Invisible Enemy Based On A Flawed Mathematical Model By Putting Me Under House Arrest Making Me Unemployed Ratting Out My Neighbour And Taking Away My Human Right,"['government', 'people', 'unemployement', 'human rights']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
According To Cnn Itocy B M Mllions Infected And Ve 1 Ou Leaths To Declare The H1 11 Flu Aeazth Emergency Ng Turnin P Ii Tu A Under President Trump Coronavirus Wa Declared A Health Emergency And Public Safety Measure Were In Place Before A Single U S Death Occurred,"['barack obama', 'donald trump', 'coronavirus', 'h1n1']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'LOC']","['H1 11', 'Trump', 'U S']"
When You Find Out That China Made Tiktok And Brought The Corona Virus L Ll Never Forgive The Chinese,"['china', 'tiktok', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Tiktok', 'Corona Virus', 'Chinese']"
Release The Vaccine What About Phase 3 Trial I Said Release It Imgflip Com,"['chef', 'vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Why Do You Always Sit Way Over There Social Distancing The Best Commentary Nemes And Humorret Poriotfost U,['social distancing'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Nemes', 'And', 'Humorret', 'Poriotfost U']"
Anatomy Of A Right Wing Meme Mother Jones,"['right wing', 'right wing']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Anatomy Of A', 'Right Wing Meme', 'Mother Jones']"
Pubg Banned In India Meanwhile Indian Parent Be Like Aakhir Wo Din Aa Hi Gya,"['pubg', 'indian parents']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['India', 'Indian', 'Aakhir']"
The British Sing God Save Our Queen The Queen Life 93 Year The British Wa Not Expecting That,"['queen', 'the queen', 'british']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['British', 'God Save Our Queen', 'Queen', 'British']"
T Wea The Masajust Dy Tre Ate Sheeple Be Like N Just A Mask S Justa Mask Ye Junt An Experimental Vaccine Misleading It Just Vaccine S Just An Implantable Microchip It S Just An Internment Camp It S Just A Microchip,"['mask', 'vaccine', 'microchip']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Don T Have To Suicide Weinstein If They Blame The China Virus,"['harvey weinstein', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Weinstein', 'China', 'Virus']"
Covid 19 Rest Of The World Today Message To This Group Are Now Secured With End To End Encryption Tap For More Info China Created Vrus Covid 19 China Added Rest Of The World China Left,"['china', 'the world', 'covid19', 'world']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Covid', 'World', 'China', 'Vrus', 'Covid', 'China', 'Rest Of The World', 'China']"
Ever Wonder What The Extra Stand For Corona Extra A Vo A Thefunnybeaver Com,"['coronavirus', 'corona extra', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['Corona', 'Com']"
When That Russian Vaccine Kick In Imaflip Com,['russian vaccine'],['B-VIL'],['MISC'],['Russian']
When You Get War On The First Day It Break Out Tam Speed China Virus Meme 2,['china virus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['China Virus Meme 2']
China Modiji Covid 19 Rula Diya Na Bechaari Ko The Indianexpres,"['china', 'covid19', 'covid 19', 'narendra modi']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Modiji Covid', 'Rula Diya Na Bechaari', 'Indianexpres']"
Nimo Enimsaden Oct 20 Unseen Footage Of Boris Johnson Offering 8 Per Head To Andy Burnham Mcan Bonel Lockdown Andy What Could It Cost 10 Pound Ta 3 O 34,"['andy burnham', 'boris johnson']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Nimo Enimsaden', 'Boris Johnson', 'Andy Burnham', 'Mcan', 'Bonel']"
They Should First Test The Covid Vaccine On Gov T Official If They Are Safe The Vaccine Is Good But If They Die The Country Is Safe,"['government officials', 'country', 'vaccine', 'government', 'covid vaccine']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Covid']
H Covid Man Relly Carried On Your Breath Why Aet Hunaha Na Thena Wy De They Misleading Wryback Of Your A Wake Up Ete Vras Is Spreadkadroef Sala Tnele Orp Of Salna Can Infect An Entrecite Ekr Hea Torle Thetsample,['covid19'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC']","['H Covid', 'Ete', 'Salna']"
Trung Say The Viras Is Uka Covid I Know More About Wind Than Yourdo And I Took That Peraonaly Cape Y E Pa Nd Aa,"['donald trump', 'covid19', 'dr  anthony fauci', 'coronavirus', 'abraham lincoln', 'joe biden']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Trung', 'Yourdo']"
We Are Not Eat Tofu Scared Yet Dumb People 2 Year From Now That Whole Coronavirus Thing Wa Overhyped I Didn T Even Die,"['coronavirus', 'tofu']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Tofu', 'Coronavirus']"
Norton Antivirus Proci,"['norton antivirus mask', 'norton antivirus antivirus', 'norton antivirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Norton Antivirus Proci']
Whole World To Putin Putin Vaccine Well Done Putinsimso Proud Of You Vaccine Vaccine,"['vladimir putin', 'vaccine', 'world']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Putin', 'Putin', 'Putinsimso']"
Joking About A New Plague Happening New Disease Start In China,"['china', 'new disease', 'plague']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
Futuristic Caveman Uturisticcavet 10H Boris Johnson S Reaction To Covid 19 Seifisolating Ojust Feel That Yknow If Itaint Broke Don T Fix It And Even If It Is Broke Just Ignore It And Maybe It L Be Sort Of Okay Gif,"['boris johnson', 'covid19', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG']","['Boris Johnson', 'Covid']"
Indian 8 G Curana Go Yesterday Rekha Ji Socurty Guard Tested Covid Postive Now Amit Ji Tosted Covd Positivatiekhatamitatebachan Aap Chronology Samajhiye Om 1203 Am Ja 12 200 O20 People Are Talng Atout Is,"['rekha', 'amitabh bachchan', 'coronavirus', 'amitabh bacchan', 'amit shah']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'PER']","['Indian', 'Rekha Ji', 'Amit Ji']"
Release The Vaccine What About Phase3 Trial I Said Release It,"['vaccine phase 3 trial', 'vaccine', 'chef']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
China Now Suffering From Hanta Virus It Originated From Rodent,"['hantavirus', 'china', 'rodents', 'hanta virus', 'chinese']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Hanta']"
I Have Corona Virus,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['I Have Corona Virus']
No Evidence Vladimir Putin Isosharing A Covo 19 Update The World S First Vaccine Aganat Coronavirus Wil Be Segissered In Russia In A Few Day Usian Scientints Passed Necessary Test Stage And Proved 1The Salety And Etfectiveness Of The Drug Cur Medione Ha Adequately Coped With The Epidemic And Now Give Hope Not Only 0 Our Country But 10 He Whole Warld Once The Soviet Satelite Prved The Way For Humarity Inno Space Now The Russian Vaccine Wil Pave The Wiy To The Uture Without Covid 19 Mask And Social Solation,"['russian scientists', 'vaccine', 'covid vaccine', 'coronavirus', 'vladimir putin', 'russia', 'vladimir putin']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Vladimir Putin', 'Covo', 'World S', 'Coronavirus', 'Russia', 'Usian', 'Soviet Satelite', 'Russian']"
5 11 2019 Usa President Taen Il Global E News A Ehte Tetie Infected Morld Dead 1 220 2 74B Just Like The Simulation,[],[],"['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG']","['Usa', 'Taen', 'Il Global E News A Ehte Tetie Infected Morld Dead']"
Breaking 3 Hr Screenrant Com Tom Hank Blood Being Used To Develop Covid Vaccine P Ll Finally Have A Friend In Me,"['tom hanks', 'covid vaccine', 'covid vaccine']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC']","['Tom Hank', 'Covid']"
China Virus Can Be Contracted Only Through Human Contact Introvert,"['introverts', 'china', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
People With Normal Flu This Is Where I M Staying This Is My Home People With Coronavirus I Travel All Around The City Golinand Out Of Locometivesoim,"['covid infected people', 'people with normal flu', 'people with coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Flu', 'Coronavirus', 'City', 'Golinand']"
Say No To Corona Virus Torona Light Tsingtao Aers,"['tsingtao beer', 'corona beer', 'coronavirus', 'tsingtao', 'corona']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Corona Virus', 'Torona Light', 'Tsingtao Aers']"
They Should First Test The Covid Vaccine On Gov T Official If They Are Safe The Vaccine Is Good But If They Die The Country Is Safe,"['government officials', 'country', 'covid vaccine']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Covid']
Just Because Thousand Of False Independent Doctor Are Saying That Hydrocyhloroquine Cure All Cv 19 Patient It Is Not Valid Until We Have A Major Study Done A Soon A The Cv 19 Vaceine Is Manufactured It Must Be Immediately Delivered To Health Care Professional World Wide For Immediate Human Injection Proper Study Can Be Performed Later,"['doctors', 'covid vaccine', 'hydroxychloroquine', 'covid vaccine', 'hydrochloroquine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
China You Think This Is Funny Reddit Making Meme Of The Virus,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'reddit', 'virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Reddit']"
Funny Coronavirus Meme The Corona Virus Won T Last Long Because It Wa Made In China Shafs,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'Corona Virus', 'China']"
When 1820 And 1920 Have Disease Outbreak And You Hear About The New Chinese Epidemic,['chinese outbreak'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Chinese']
Twitter Safety Twittersa 2H In Addition We Will 1 No Longer Serve Content And Account Associated With Qanon In Trend And Recommendation 2 Work To Ensure We Re Not Highlighting This Activity In Search And Conversation 3 Block Url Associated With Qanon From Being Shared On Twitter Ganons We Need To Dig Deeper,"['twitter', 'qanon']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL']",[],[]
Beshram Memer Obeshram Memer After Successfully Human Trial Of Coronavaccine By Russia Putin And Scientist Research Team Be Like Russianvaccine,"['russian vaccine', 'russian scientists', 'russia vaccine', 'corona vaccine', 'vladimir putin', 'scientists', 'russia', 'research']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'PER', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Beshram Memer', 'Obeshram Memer', 'Coronavaccine', 'Russia', 'Putin', 'Scientist', 'Russianvaccine']"
Roz Subah Utho Nahao China Se Aayi Nayi Virus Ke Bare Meln Padho Or Soo Jao,['china'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Roz', 'Subah', 'China Se', 'Ke', 'Or']"
John Fugelsang Johnfugelsang Well I M Not Surprised Trump Tested Positive For Covid The Guy S In 5 Major Risk Group 1 He S Elderly 2 He S Obese 3 He S Got A Public Sector Job 4 He S A Person Of Color 5 He S Poor Prayfortrump To Wearadamnmask,"['donald trump', 'coronavirus', 'donald trump']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER']","['John Fugelsang', 'Johnfugelsang', 'Trump', 'Covid']"
1720 1820 And 1920 Have Massive Plague Outbreak Not Even A Month Into 2020 Worid News Tarker Tody China S Mysterious Virus Outbreak Grows With 139 Case Reported Over Two Day Im Beginning To See A Pattern Here That Im Not So Sure I Like,"['plague', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC']","['Tarker', 'Tody', 'China']"
Coronavirus Spread Me Realizing My Shirt Is Made In China Get This Sit Off Me,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China']"
1 The W Se Inistr Fore Wa Trump Anger China With Chinese Virus Tweet,"['donald trump', 'china']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC']","['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Trump', 'China', 'Chinese']"
This Is Donald Trump S Face Under His Mask Imgtip Com,"['mask', 'donald trump']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG']","['Donald Trump', 'Imgtip Com']"
Play It A Safe Don T Worry Leave Our Border Pen 2 Cote Shut Our Border To China Now 98 Leave Them Open Close Them Now This Poll Ha Ended 33 8K Vote,['china'],['B-VIL'],"['MISC', 'LOC']","['Border', 'China']"
Spread Of Deadly Coronavirus Map Reveals Spread Of Killer Bug Making Meme About China S Korea 1 Case 471 Case 17 Death Japan 1 Case China Usa 1 Case Getting The Plague Taiwan 1 Case Hong Kong 2 Case Mexico 1 Unconfirmed Thailand 4 Case Macau 1 Case Australia 1 Suspected Case The Plague Is Now In The U Screwd,"['china', 'usa', 'plague', 'us']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China', 'S Korea', 'Japan', 'China', 'Usa', 'Taiwan', 'Hong Kong', 'Mexico', 'Thailand', 'Macau', 'Australia']"
They Say You Should Wear A Mask I Don T Need A Mask I M Healthy Great The Covidiots Heard You,"['covidiots', 'donald trump', 'american people']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Covidiots']
Run Godzilla S Attacking The City Relax He S Only Killed 4000 People The Flu Kill Over 25 000 Every Y Ar Posted In R Funny By U Trippy Styx666 O Reddit,"['flu', 'godzilla']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Godzilla', 'Reddit']"
Bors Aohons Con Potey Soma Alyou May The Corona Virus We Re Meant To Die From Dimate Change 10 Make Assie Stuff For Aucsies,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Bors Aohons Con', 'Potey', 'Soma Alyou', 'Corona Virus']"
Russia Register 1St Coronavirusvaccine In The World U S Hose Down Russian Vaccine And Say It Will Have Million Of Dos Ready Year S End Imgflip Com,"['russia', 'coronavirus vaccine', 'usa', 'vaccine', 'us']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Russia', 'Coronavirusvaccine', 'U S', 'Russian']"
January February March April May July,[],[],[],[]
After Quarantine You Will Either Look Like You Want Eat Up A Ponos You Want To Or Beat Up Thanos Othegoanyao,"['thanos', 'ponos']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER']","['Ponos', 'Thanos Othegoanyao']"
Chinese Virologist Dr Li Meng Yan Coronavirus Created In A Govt Lab In Wuhan Say Whistleblower Comedy Aaaand She S Gone,"['china', 'wuhan', 'donald trump', 'lei meng yan', 'coronavirus', 'whistleblower']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'LOC']","['Chinese', 'Li Meng Yan', 'Wuhan']"
I Happen To Think Fauci S A Great Guy On The Other Hand He Changed His Mind About Masksi But When You Think About It Voter Might Like A Nice Mask Well Reasoned,"['donald trump', 'voters', 'dr  anthony fauci']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Fauci', 'Masksi']"
Itook The Liberty Of Bullshittin Yal Andyou Say Riar Riar Pant On Fire,['xi jinping'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Itook', 'Liberty Of Bullshittin Yal Andyou', 'Riar Riar Pant']"
I Think Ilook Good Wearing It Just Like The Lone Ranger,"['mask', 'donald trump', 'lone ranger']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC']","['Ilook', 'Lone Ranger']"
U Suffocating In Mask In The Time Of Covid 19 Kakashi Suffocating In Mask For His Entire Life,"['covid19', 'usa', 'mask', 'kakashi', 'kakashi hatake', 'us']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'PER']","['U', 'Covid', 'Kakashi']"
Extrovert Outside Armed With Mask And Hand Sanitizer Constantly Taking Risk Of Contracting And Spreading The Coronavirus Cdc Introvert With Crippling Depression And Social Anxiety Already Barricaded In Their Home For Month Prior To The First Outbreak Air,"['extroverts', 'introverts', 'coronavirus', 'mask', 'hand santitizer', 'outbreak']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
When You Re Out Of Toilet Paper But A Kitten Walk Into The Room I M Sorry Little One,"['kitten', 'toilet paper']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Kitten']
Heart Disease Is The Number One Cause Of Death Did You Know That Thats A Badge Of Honor Because We Will Beat That Believe Me,['donald trump'],['B-VIL'],[],[]
When You Re On A Crowded Mrt And Someone Start Coughing,['mass rapid transit  mrt '],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Everybody Hate On Supply Untilde Corona Virus Strike,"['toilet papers', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Corona']
State Alright We Re Going To Open Back Up Covid 19 Jongaldbeng,"['covid19', 'coronavirus', 'usa']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Over My Dead Body Will They Get Me To Take That Vaccine,"['vaccine', 'covid vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Hope They Allow U Off Lockdown Byjuly 4Th So We Can Celebrate Our Freedom,[],[],[],[]
Impeaches Usa,['donald trump'],['B-OTH'],['PER'],['Usa']
Nont Ask Re Ask China,"['china', 'tshirt', 't shirt']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'LOC']","['Nont Ask Re Ask', 'China']"
First Day Back To School After Lockdown Visit Patriotpo0St U For The Best Humor And Meme,[],[],[],[]
I Didn T Even Realize I Spent My Childhood Playing With Corona Virus,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Corona Virus']
Captain American After Wielding The Mjolnire Outside,"['mjolnir', 'captain america']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Captain', 'American', 'Mjolnire']"
Were In Nur Tin To Deteat The W S And Rny Peopie Say Tat Ict Veera Tace K Whes You Tance There K Nolody O Paiote Me Your Vesitent Yeah This Is Big Grain Time,['donald trump'],['B-OTH'],['LOC'],['Nur Tin']
Waiting For The Laua Like A Swede Before Corona During Corona,"['swede', 'coronavirus', 'corona']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Laua', 'Swede', 'Corona', 'Corona']"
Cnn Reporter Who Attacked Trump For Not Wearing Mask Caught Removing Mask When Camera Stop Rolling H,"['cnn reporter', 'donald trump']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Trump']
Steve King 4 Hr O According To Cnn It Took Obama Mllions Infected And Over 1 000 Death To Declare The Hin1 Flu A Health Emergency Turning P Int Usa Under President Trump Coronavirus Wa Declared A Health Emergency And Public Safety Measure Were In Place Before A Single U S Death Occurred 1 6K 269 Comment 1K Share,"['donald trump', 'barack obama', 'cnn', 'coronavirus', 'h1n1', 'h1n1 flu']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'LOC']","['Steve King', 'Obama', 'Hin1', 'Trump', 'U S']"
Week 4 Week 10,['quarantine week'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Answer To All Question About The Coming School Year Chighsondiowsolalancher I Dont Know,[],[],[],[]
Melz Mvazquez17 Me Sending My Dog Out For Supply Since He Can T Contract Covid 19 Logot Coc Gif 10 04 Am Mar 13 2020 Twitter For Iphone,"['covid19', 'dog', 'dogs', 'covid 19']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG']","['Melz Mvazquez17', 'Iphone']"
A The Cdc Continaes To Study The Spread Of The Covid 19 They Ecommend That People Wear Cloth Face Covering In Public Setting Where Social Distancing Measure Can Be Difficult To Maintain Remember This Doe Not Replace The Importance Of Ocial Distancing Ii Is Recommended To Koep U All Safe Flotus Melania Trump,"['melania trump', 'coronavirus', 'face mask', 'centre of disease control  cdc ']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'ORG', 'PER']","['Covid', 'Koep', 'U', 'Melania Trump']"
Trump Defends Use Of Phrase China Virus Despite Demand From China To Stop China Ha Now Renamed Syphilis Trump Virus Imgflip Com,"['donald trump', 'china', 'syphilis', 'china virus', 'trump virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Trump', 'China', 'China', 'China', 'Syphilis Trump Virus']"
Actual Footage Of Teacher If They Hear A Student Cough In Their Classroom Estudentsaywhat,"['air freshner', 'students', 'teacher', 'teachers', 'student']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Sour Sour258 Indian Cook Getting Boycotted For Selling Indian Chinese Gobi Manchurian,['indian cook'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Indian', 'Indian Chinese', 'Gobi Manchurian']"
Watching Someone Waste Soap Ber Bernie Watching Someone Waste Handwash Watching Someone Bern Waste Sanitizer Watching Someone Waste Urrak Inie Generzy,"['urrak', 'sanitizer', 'bernie sanders', 'soap', 'handwash']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Urrak']
Ileo Ane Covid 19 Is A Lie Nfd A Trump Supporter In California Hold A Sign Saying Covid 19 Is A Lie While A Mask And Hazmat Suit,"['donald trump', 'california', 'covid19', 'hazmat suit', 'tump supporter', 'mask', 'donald trump supporter']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Ileo', 'Ane Covid', 'Trump', 'California', 'Covid', 'Hazmat']"
R Murderedbywords Trumputin Is Something I Ship Oc 1 6 9 1 6 1 Dr Anthony Fauci Unveils A Mask That Could Save Million Of Life Politics Pic Gifs House 1 16 4K I 726 1 Share A Award Y Best Comment 2Awards Why Doesn T He Just Wear The Ball Gag He Us With Putin 1 538 11 Share O Award I Hate R Murderedbywords With A Burning Passion Haha Trump Gay For Putin,"['dr  anthony fauci', 'anthony fauci', 'donald trump', 'valdimir puitin', 'mask', 'vladimir putin', 'vladimir putin']","['B-HERO', 'B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC']","['Trumputin', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Gifs House', 'Putin', 'Haha', 'Trump', 'Putin']"
Wear A Mask The Same Way Exit He Handle The Pandemic Makeameme Org,"['donald trump', 'mask']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Mask', 'Pandemic', 'Org']"
God Dam It Carl,[],[],"['PER', 'PER']","['God', 'Carl']"
There Is A Much More Sinister Reason Why China Let The Virus Go And Withheld Information A Pelosi Said China Prefers Biden To Win The Election Where S Hunter Will Hunter Be Suicided Like Epstein Imgflip Com,"['china', 'joe biden', 'hunter biden', 'nancy peloci', 'jeffrey epstein', 'virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['China', 'A', 'Pelosi', 'China', 'Biden', 'Epstein', 'Com']"
Killed By Alcohol Temperature Above 57 Degree I Worldofbuzz Com Expert Say Deadly Wuhan Virus Can Be Killed By Alcohol High Temperature Doctor I Used The Corona To Destroy The Corona,"['doctor', 'wuhan virus', 'doctors', 'coronavirus', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan', 'Alcohol', 'Corona', 'Corona']"
Oh Wa I Speeding Officer,['toilet paper'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Oh Wa']
When The People Of Wuhan Are Wondering Why There S Only 1 Plane Coming To Disinfect The City China Exterminates The Coronavirus In Wuhan 2020,"['china', 'wuhan people', 'wuhan', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Wuhan', 'China', 'Coronavirus', 'Wuhan']"
First China Got Corona Now U Let Go,"['china', 'usa', 'coronavirus', 'africa']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['First', 'China', 'Corona']"
Expert Say Deadly Wuhan Virus Can Be Killed By Alcohol High Temperature Killed By Alcohol Temperature Above 57 Degree Corona Extra Coronavirus Duotu Expert Say Deadly Wuhan Virus Can Be Killed By Alcohol Amp High Temperature,"['doctor', 'wuhan virus', 'china', 'coronavirus', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan', 'Coronavirus', 'Duotu', 'Wuhan']"
Donald Trump Jr Igger June 30 At 5 35 Pm Solid Point This Is What Virologist Wear To Protect Themselves From A Virus Don T Worry Though Your Bandana Probably Work Too,"['virus', 'virologist', 'bandana']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Donald Trump']
Chinese Woman Dodge Airport Screening In France Traveller Told To Heed Check For Wuhan Virus What An Idiot What A Idiotic Idiot,"['wuhan virus', 'airport', 'coronavirus', 'chinese woman', 'wuhan', 'france', 'travellers']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Chinese', 'Dodge Airport', 'France', 'Wuhan']"
When A Chinese Dude Sneeze Right Next To You Mcb Mr Stark I Don T Feel So Good I Don T Wan Na Go Mr Stark Please,"['chinese', 'mr stark', 'chinese dude', 'spiderman']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'PER']","['Chinese', 'Stark', 'Stark']"
Say Hello To The 46Th President Doe Exotic,['donald trump'],['B-OTH'],['PER'],['Doe Exotic']
Aw Geez It S Not Like He Called It The Chink Virus,"['china', 'chink virus', 'donald trump']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chink']
When You Were About To Finish A Long And Annoying Task But Then Some Jerk Report A Dead Body Memezila Com,"['muhammad sarim akhtar', 'among us']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Memezila Com']
Democrat Weneed To Lockdown To Save Livesi What The Lockdown Are Doing So 130 Million People Could Starve Because Of The Lockdown News Covid Could Push 265 Million People To Starvation If Action Not Taken Un Covid 19 Linked Hunger Cauld Cause More Death Than The Disease Itself New Report Find I Call That Empathy And Compassion,"['coronavirus', 'lockdown', 'democrats', 'people', 'united nations', 'united nations  un ']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC']","['Democrat', 'Livesi', 'Covid']"
How To Avoid Ur Annoying Relative This Cny Post On Fb Just Backfrom Wuhan,"['chinese new year', 'relatives', 'wuhan', 'facebook']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['Wuhan']
It S For Your Own Good You Ve Got To Stop Touching Your Face P,[],[],[],[]
I Just Want To Say One Thing About Coronavirus This Is The Longest Something Made In China Ha Ever Lasted,"['made in china', 'china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China']"
When You Catch The China Virus But You Already Have Aid Let Them Fight,"['aids', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['China Virus']
The Impostor Pretending To Fix The Sabotage He Did 3 Second Ago,[],[],[],[]
Corona Virus Just Callit The China Virus That S Where It Came From,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Corona Virus', 'The China Virus']"
When You Dont Have A Ps4 But Still Get To Play Biohazard 8,"['chinese people', 'biohazard 8', 'ps4']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Biohazard']
Me Trying To Do Anything On The Internet Are You Registered To Vote,[],[],[],[]
A Coronavirus Case Spike Worldwide China Is Closing Itself Off By James Grifmths Cnn Updated 9 15 Am Edt Fri March 27 2020 You Re About Frve Year Too Late,"['china', 'cnn', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'PER']","['Coronavirus', 'Spike Worldwide', 'China', 'James Grifmths']"
Usa Never Ask A Woman We Have The Highest Amount Her Age Of Covidis Case In The World A Man China His Salary The Chinese Government You Have The Highest Amount Of Reported Case The Of Po Wecd Wh Caronevi,"['chinese government', 'usa', 'china', 'covid 19 cases', 'covid19 cases', 'woman', 'man']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Usa', 'Covidis', 'Chinese', 'Caronevi']"
Best Candidate For 2020 Joe Biden Kamala Harris Bernie Sanders Tikto Deliguthrie,"['joe biden', 'bernie sanders', 'bernie sanders', 'kamala harris']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER']","['Joe Biden', 'Kamala Harris', 'Bernie Sanders', 'Tikto Deliguthrie']"
Don T Know What Ya Got Til It S Gone Waffle House Rale Ouse,['waffle house'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['House']
Reaking News Blow Job Kill Coronavirus Fected Person Ha Symptom An Nba Legend Kobe Bryan Neww,"['china', 'herald newspaper', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER']","['Nba', 'Kobe Bryan Neww']"
A New Lethal Virus Start Spreading Africa No What Sorry Force Of Habit China No Nam,"['word health organisation', 'china', 'africa', 'world health organization  who ']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC']","['Africa', 'China']"
When Died Due To Corona You Virus And Again Born In China,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'baby']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Corona', 'China']"
The Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'chinese coronavirus', 'kung flu']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu']
Citizen You Can T Just Let U Die The Government This Is American Boredpanda Com,"['american government', 'american citizens', 'usa government', 'us government', 'us citizens', 'citizens']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Government', 'American', 'Com']"
Actual Footage Teachar Tech Time Com Tru Of Teacher Trying To Get Through 2020,['teachers'],['B-VIC'],[],[]
Stop Paranoia,[],[],[],[]
How You Think You Look Protesting The Lockdown How You Actually Look Protesting The Lockdown Help Help I M Being Repressed,"['protestors', 'lockdown']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Taking Coronavirus Seriously Ustening To Public Health Expert Golf And Campaign Rally,"['donald trump', 'campaign rallies', 'golf', 'coronavirus', 'public health experts']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Coronavirus', 'Rally']"
Knight Is Back Hit Tv For Revenge Wednesday January 29 2020 1 90 Heraldsun Com Au We Re Foryou Minister Slam School For Turning Ldren Away Corona Chaos Chinese Virus Pandamonium Fearful Of The Ashley Argoon And Have Been Grant Mcarthur Advice And Tly Visi And Infectious Di Victorian Sch Deadly Coronavirus Slammed For Defying M Banning Healthy Kid Wh Ted China From Retuming To At Least 15 School And Kinderga Have Ordered Family Who Bolidayed In The Outbreak City Of Wuhan Or Any Said Any Advice That Contradicts This Where In China And Even Hong Kong Cdear And Expert Medical Advice Creates And Taiwan To Keep Child At Home But The Nation S Chief Medical Officer Continued Page 4 Perts Unani Ght That Only Those Mgtoms Posed A Threat Education Minister James Merlino Confusion And Frustration Force Not,"['china', 'herald newspaper', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'PER']","['Knight', 'Chinese', 'Coronavirus', 'China', 'Wuhan', 'China', 'Hong Kong', 'Taiwan', 'James Merlino']"
The Daily Show Trump S Cringey Coronavirus Address,"['donald trump', 'picture', 'trevor noah', 'the daily show', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['The Daily Show Trump S']
You Should Remember This From Your 1L Contract Class This Is Just A Review From Civ Pro I M Assuming You Learned This In Your Legal Writing Class Now Who Can Quickly Summaize Jreen Basie Il Concept Here,[],[],"['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Civ', 'Jreen', 'Basie', 'Il']"
Bernie Or Pete Tein Compae Them On The In Ihat Issue Yo Can I Borrow Ur Charger Sorry I Nibbled Iam Once Again Asking For Your Financial Support Yea Sure Little Hole In Mine And It Doesn T Work Anymore,"['bernie sanders', 'pete buttigieg']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Bernie', 'Pete Tein']"
Gpan Gricatapie Weed Kill Corona Virus Scientist Are Shocked To Discover That Weed Kill Corona Virus Coronavirus Coronavirus Live Breaking News Weed Kill Corona Virus Scientist Are Shocked To Discover That Weed Kill Corona Virus 458 Am Feb 4 2020 Titie Oravaoe,"['weed', 'coronavirus']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER']","['Gpan Gricatapie', 'Corona', 'Corona', 'Corona', 'Corona', 'Titie Oravaoe']"
Money Heist Le Professor,"['money heist', 'professor']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Professor']
Dovoubonald Com Cooyoudonaldc Can T Die Of Covid If You Kill Yourself Trump Meme Is This A Vaccine,"['donald trump', 'lysol', 'vaccine', 'covid', 'lisol', 'lizol', 'covid vaccine']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Dovoubonald Com', 'Cooyoudonaldc', 'Trump Meme']"
Other Country Fighting Coronavirus The U Starting A Civil War,"['us', 'other countries', 'coronavirus', 'usa']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'U']"
Let See Who S Really Behind Covid 19 Zoom,"['zoom', 'covid19', 'china']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['Covid', 'Zoom']"
Me Trying To Catch Up On Some Sleep In The Morning Zoom Meeting,"['zoom meeting', 'zoom']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Parenting During The Coronavirus Shutdown Day 1 Day 3,"['parenting', 'parents', 'alcohol', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
Me After Washing My Hand For 20 Second 57 Time In One Day,[],[],[],[]
Working From Home Be Like News Bmyjesusjam,['bbc news'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Bmyjesusjam']
Kid Who Have Been Learning Common Core Math About To Learn How To Carry The 1 From Their New Homeschool Teacher,"['teacher', 'student']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Common Core']
Hell No Why Myself Or My Kid Will Never Get The Flue Shot One Of The Many Reason Texas 14 Year Old Virgin Fall Pregnant After Flu Shot Worldnewsdailyreport Com The Guy Who Fucked Her Maybe L Am A Vaccine,"['vaccine', 'texas', 'flu vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Worldnewsdailyreport Com']
This Trump Mask Look Like Hitler From The Back,"['donald trump', 'mask', 'adolf hitler']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Trump', 'Hitler']"
Whet Are You Waiting For I Don T Know For Yoo To He Normal I Guess Me Too Kid,"['usa', 'the world', 'us', 'world']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
When You Re Raising The Mexican Flag And Protesting Trump And An Ice Truck Pass By,"['donald trump', 'u s  immigration and customs enforcement s  ice ', 'mexicans', 'ice truck', 'mexican flag']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC']","['Mexican Flag', 'Trump', 'Truck']"
In Other News Kid Are Going Back To School,"['school', 'kids', 'news']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Covid Is Rampant Because People Not Wearing Mask The Flu Is Nonexistent Because Of Mask The Cdc,"['centre for disease control  cdc ', 'covid19', 'flu', 'coronavirus', 'mask', 'cdc']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Covid']
When Trump Said I Wear A Mask I Don T Wear A Mask Like Him Every Time You See Him He S Got A Mask He Could Be Speaking 200Ft Away From Me And He Show Up With The Biggest Mask You Ve Ever Seen,"['mask', 'donald trump', 'joe biden']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Trump']
Me I Guess I Could Handle 4 Week Of Quarantine Government 4 4 2 2,['government'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Me', 'Handle', 'Week Of', 'Government']"
China Gave Hunter Billion China Gave The Planet Covid 19 Work For Me,"['china', 'joe biden', 'covid19', 'world', 'coronavirus', 'hunter biden', 'covid 19']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC']","['China', 'China']"
Me I Guess I Could Handle 4 Week Of Quarantine Government Hehe 4 4 4,['government'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Hehe']
De Sele Sont This Is What Virologist Wear To Protect Themselves From A Virus Don T Worry Though Your Bandana Probably Work Too,"['bandana', 'virologists', 'mask', 'virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Covid 19 Covid 19 Covid 19 Covid 19 D Tar Cop Cond I,"['covid 19', 'covid19']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Covid', 'Covid', 'Covid', 'Covid', 'D Tar Cop']"
The Cdc Want You To Wear A Mask In Public It Not About The Virus They Re Just Tired Of Looking At Your Ugly Face Makeamame Org,"['donald trump', 'centre for disease control  cdc ', 'coronavirus', 'mask', 'cdc']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['Cdc', 'Org']"
When You Find Out Your Daily Lifestyle Is Actually Called Quarantine,['quarantine'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Trump Wore A Maski We Hate Mask Now,"['donald trump', 'mask']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC']","['Trump', 'Maski']"
When You Turn Around And A Student Is Gin Away From You Instead Of Gft,['student'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Trump Tried To Get Away With Only Wearing His Mask When The Press Wasnt Around Someone From Tmz Wa Around Though,"['donald trump', 'tmz', 'tmz news', 'press']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Trump']
Masksp I Don T Think Im Going To Be Doing It It Would Send The Wrong Message It Make You Look Like A Wimp The Virus Is Just Gon Na Disappear 100 000 Dead People Later Iam All For Mask Always Have Been Wear Them All The Time Ilike It,"['donald trump', 'mask', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Without Corona The Medium Lie And The Government Is Corrupt With Corona Let Believe Everything The Medium Tell U And Do Whatever Our Ruler Tell U To Do Ofo Com,"['media', 'government', 'media house', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG']","['Corona', 'Corona', 'Com']"
Trump Trump Finally Remove His Human Mask And Reveals His Hideously Deformed Alien Form,"['donald trump', 'mask', 'alien']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Trump', 'Trump']"
Joe Meakin X So You Ll Be Boycotting Them Now Iam Pro Oxygen Sweet Beautiful Oxygen Nhiberals M 20 Itter For Android,"['liberals', '', 'donald trump', 'oxygen']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Joe Meakin']
Let S Go To The Winchester Have A Pint And Wait For The Coronavirus Blo It S Shut,"['coronavirus', 'winchester']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC']","['Winchester', 'Coronavirus']"
Marty Whatever Happens Dont Ever Go To 2020,"['2020', 'marty']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Marty']
How T Expected My Apocolypse Outfit To Look What It Is,['apocalypse outfit'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Apocolypse']
Trump Look At This Hillary Mask It S Hidecus Just Like Her Sou Aide Whisper In Ear Trump This Mask Is Beautiful Breathtaking,"['donald trump', 'hillary clinton', 'mask']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC']","['Trump', 'Hillary Mask', 'Trump', 'Mask']"
Am I The Only One Around Here That Think Who Director General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus Should Be Charged With Manslaughter,"['tedros adhanom ghebreyesus', 'world health organization  who ']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus']
House Dr Fauci Unveils A Mask That Could Save Million Of Life,"['dr  anthony fauci', 'donald trump', 'mask']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Fauci']
Rie Nreess Reporter Is There Any Evidence To Suggest That A With Malaria It Might Be Used A A Prophylaxis Against Covid 19,"['donald trump', 'reporter', 'dr  anthony fauci', 'coronavirus', 'malaria']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Rie Nreess', 'Malaria', 'Covid']"
Hows 2020 So Far Kobe Died Australia Wa On Fire The Whole Country Covid 19 Shut Down But We Got 4 20 All Month In April,"['2020', 'kobe bryant', 'country', 'australia', 'covid19', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'LOC']","['Kobe', 'Australia']"
Everyone Hand Washing Disinfection Literally Any Mask The Guardian,"['mask', 'hand wash', 'the guardian']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['The Guardian']
President Trump Epotus U Government Account 45Th President Of The United State Of American Tweet Archived Wh Go O Washington D C Whitehous Gov Jained January 2017 39 Fallowing 33 4M Folowers,"['us government', 'donald trump', 'usa']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Trump', 'U', 'United State', 'American', 'Washington D C', 'Whitehous']"
He S Been Wearing One This Whole Time It S Like Wearing Nothing At All 1999 Trump Eac,"['mask', 'donald trump']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Trump Eac']
Mu1 Che W Se Inistr Fore Trumpangers China With Chinese Virus Tweet,"['donald trump', 'china', 'chinese virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Mu1', 'China', 'Chinese']"
Trump Had Been Advised By His Staff To Wear A Mask They Weren T Nearly Specific Enough Ca D,"['mask', 'donald trump', 'donald trump s staff']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['Trump']
Work From Home Meme Your Manager When The Work Which Take 15 Minute Ha Not Been Submitted From More Than An Hour Because The Employee Is On Work From Home So Daya Kuch Toh Gardbad Hai Redit Gandalfdgrey Unsplash Representative Image,"['employee', 'boss', 'cid']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Gardbad Hai', 'Gandalfdgrey']"
You Have Tested Positive For Covid 19,"['donald trump', 'covid19', 'dr  anthony fauci']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Getting Ready In The Morning Bec Ause Your Job Won T Close In The Middle Of A Pandemic,[],[],['MISC'],['Pandemic']
Alot Of Wods Pecete Check Bamgi Pa Tid Ve Compiesi Gor A Sreakingnews Weed Killscorona Virus Weedkillscorona Virus,"['weed', 'coronavirus']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Waiting To Hear My School District S Plan For Fall,[],[],[],[]
2020 Is Gon Na Be My Year Coronavirus,"['coronavirus', '2020']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Na', 'Coronavirus']"
Se Departrent Uging U Criaens Not To Tevel By Cruse U Navy,"['us navy', 'us citizens']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['U Criaens', 'U Navy']"
Peraps Touve Come To Eplain Thi2 Enaps Touve Come To Tel Me Why My Sen Brid Ow Did You Escape And Ht Son Did Notp Wett Tt Th To Strle Rel To Emon Th Nm T T You A Wisc Hithaanr Tla Jmtttes Erm Tretkat Ba Tl The Authority Is Not Yours To Deny The Return Of The King Steward The Rule Of Gondor Is Mine And No Other S,[],[],"['PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Peraps Touve', 'Touve', 'Hithaanr', 'Gondor']"
Good Example Of Social Distancing Bad Example Of Social Distancing Ct Alarama,"['social distancing', 'gondor']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['Alarama']
Meanwhile In Afghanistan Wtf Is Toilet Paper,"['afghanistan', 'toilet paper']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['Afghanistan']
Work From Home Expectation Reality,['work from home'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Looking At The Map To Get Some Travel Idea For The Weekend Visit Patriotpost U For The Best Humorand Meme,[],[],['ORG'],['Patriotpost U']
Meme Insurgent Mother Nature Humanity Deadly Wuhan Virus,"['mother nature', 'humanity', 'wuhan virus', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'humans', 'nature']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Meme', 'Nature', 'Wuhan Virus']"
Wor The Pandemic Represents A Rare But Narrow Window Econe Of Opportunity To Reflect Reimagine And Reset Our Foru World Klaus Schwab,['klaus schwab'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'PER']","['Foru', 'Klaus Schwab']"
Protect Yourself From Virus 20 Day Shipping From Wuhan China Every Mask Ha Been Human Tested In Our Wuhan Factory For Quality Assurance 50 Off Xdoubt,"['china', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'mask', 'wuhan']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Wuhan', 'China', 'Wuhan']"
Trump Defends Use Of Phrase China Virus Despite Demand From China To Stop China Ha Now Renamed Syphilis Trump Virus Olo Com,"['donald trump', 'china', 'syphilis', 'china virus', 'trump virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Trump', 'China', 'China', 'China', 'Syphilis Trump Virus Olo Com']"
New Book 00 Please Note The Post Apocalyptical Fiction Section Ha Been Moved To Current Affair The Best Humorand Meme Are At Patriotpost U,['books'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'LOC']","['Post Apocalyptical Fiction', 'Patriotpost U']"
Hey Babe Just Thought You Should Know There Sa Contirmed Case Of Corona In Cur Neighborhood Ere Re Orgytung Brenhe Ete Holy Shit You Re Kiding Brny Sck Nion Ee E Ton Baomer Men Lmati E What The Tuck Is Wrong With You Aanet,"['corona beer', 'coronavirus', 'corona']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Corona', 'Nion']"
Killed By Alcohole Temperature Above S7Oegresi Worldocom Expert Say Deadly Wuhan Virus Can Be Killed By Alcohol High Temperature Corona Corona,"['wuhan virus', 'coronavirus', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'scientists', 'wuhan', 'alcohol', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Alcohole', 'Worldocom', 'Wuhan', 'Corona']"
Government Urge People To Work From Home During The Pandemic Uber Driver,"['uber drivers', 'uber', 'government']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Pandemic']
Found At A Park In Brooklyn Nyc Like The Masx Ya Ganna Hate The Ventilator O Weirdworldinsta,"['new york city', 'mask', 'ventilator', 'brooklyn']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Park', 'Brooklyn', 'O']"
Day 1Without Football Day 10 Day 30,['football'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Me And My Coworkers Logging Into All Of Our Meeting Remotely For The Next Couple Of Week,[],[],[],[]
Breaking News Urgent Notice Coronavirus Update The Cdc Is Encouraging Everyone To Get Tested Asap The U Is Taking The Corona Virus Very Seriously New Testing Method Are Being Done Without Having To Leave Your House No Hospital Visit Necessary Allyou Have To Do Is Mail A Stool Sample To Nancy Pelos 1326 Longworth H O B Washington Dc 20125,"['usa', 'coronavirus', 'nancy pelosi', 'cdc']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'Corona Virus', 'Nancy Pelos', 'Longworth', 'Washington']"
If You Don T Need A Mask Because God Will Protect You You Dont Need An Assault Rifle For The Same Reason,"['mask', 'god', 'assault rifle']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['PER'],['God']
Nobody Youtube Recommendation 8 11 Clueless White Guy Order In Perfect Chinese I Shock Patron And Staff Xinomanye Tala 1 V T Week Age,"['youtube', 'white guy', 'chinese']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Chinese', 'Xinomanye Tala']"
Yes I Work From Home How Did You Know,[],[],[],[]
Government Work From Home Lifeguard,"['lifeguards', 'government']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
This Shit Is Why The Alien Won T Talk To U,['aliens'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Alien']
Chinese Woman Dodge Airport Screening In France Traveller Told To Heed Check For Wuhan Virus What An Idiot What A Idiotic Idiot,"['wuhan virus', 'chinese woman', 'airport', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'france', 'travellers']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Chinese', 'Dodge Airport', 'France', 'Wuhan']"
Ieme Insurgent Mother Deadly Nature Wuhan Virus Humanity,"['mother nature', 'humanity', 'wuhan virus', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'humans', 'nature']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Ieme Insurgent', 'Mother', 'Nature', 'Wuhan', 'Virus Humanity']"
Why Are You Wearing A Surgical Mask I M Not It S A Coughy Filter,['surgical mask'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Democrat When We Assume Them Taking Office Will Bring The End Of Covid,"['democrats', 'covid19']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Democrat', 'Covid']"
Soution Ta A Lot Of Word Problerm Lein Ndia Ut You Cant D Them A Long A You Ridicae Our Ancet Wdom Fact Check Caiis Lo T A Seby Gevt Lecene Of Ar Gardard Tem Pharma Company Etad A Make Cann Weed Killscorona Virus,"['weed', 'coronavirus']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Caiis Lo', 'Ar Gardard Tem Pharma Company', 'Etad A']"
They Are Never Going Back To School,['teachers'],['B-VIC'],[],[]
Yeah This Is The Guy Thatis Going To Save U From Coronavirus Critieal Spaee Fght Hardware Do Not Touchr We Re All Doomed,"['joe biden', 'mike pence', 'dr  anthony fauci', 'coronavirus', 'people']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
2020 Is Here But You Realize That 1720 1820 And 1920 Had A Massive Plague Outbreak Agmaghoy Look Like Plague S Back On The Menu Boy,"['plague', 'plague outbreak']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Agmaghoy']
Nnevvy Applause To Thai From Hong Kong Why Thai Did Not Get Hurt,"['thais', 'china', 'hong kong', 'thailand']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Nnevvy', 'Thai', 'Hong Kong', 'Thai']"
Corona Virus China Virus Meme War Imgflip Com,"['xi jinping', 'donald trump', 'china', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Corona Virus', 'China', 'War', 'Com']"
You Can Cry You Can Scream Liberal Plan To Scream At Sky Over Trump Headline News But The Left Can T Meme Ngli N,"['liberals', 'left', 'donald trump']","['B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Liberal', 'Trump']"
When It S Finally 2020 But You Realize That Both 1820 And 1920 Had Massive Plague Outbreak Hmm Fuck,"['plague', 'plague outbreaks']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
When My Roomate Who Just Came Back From Visiting Family In China Tell Me She S Feeling A Bit Sick,['china'],['B-VIL'],['LOC'],['China']
Cari Kelemen Kelemencari New Year S Eve Wuhan V Time Square A56 Pm 12 31 20 Twitter Web App,"['wuhan', 'times square', 'carl elemen']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Cari', 'Kelemen', 'Kelemencari', 'Year', 'Eve', 'Wuhan', 'Time Square']"
Me About 2020 Ctacrir Meme R Tried Writing A Song About It But I Can T Think Of Anything That Rhyme With Aarrgghhi,"['2020', 'people', 'everyone', 'kids']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Ctacrir', 'Aarrgghhi']"
When All The Kid Go Back To School After Being Homeschooled Ma Ma M M Mama Said,"['school', 'kids', 'homeschooled']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
What If We Can Breath In Space But The Government Just Tellsus We Cant So We Don T Try To Escape,"['government', 'people']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC']",[],[]
Half Of My Friend Right Now I Want To Play Ludo King With You Qmemes Of Gon Mog,['ludo king'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'MISC']","['Ludo King', 'Gon Mog']"
Corona Virus Pandemic Daylight Saving Time Friday The 13Th And A Full Moon All In The Same Week Who The Hell Is Playing Jumanji,"['jumanji', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Corona Virus Pandemic', 'Moon', 'Jumanji']"
A Photographer Took Picture Of People Before And After Telling Them They Had Coronavirus,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
Novel Coronavirus Ha Human To Human Transmission Introvert Celebrate Like A Bos Introvert Will Rule The Worid,"['introverts', 'coronavirus transmission', 'coronavirus']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Coronavirus', 'Bos']"
When You Find Out Your Cousin Is An Asian At Least Corona Virus Won T Last Long Because It Wa Made In China,"['asian', 'china', 'asian people', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Asian', 'China']"
China Is Where The Virus Originated China Silenced Whistleblower And Covered It Up China Lied To The World About The Extent Of The Outbreak China Refused Offer Of Help In Containing The Virus China Infected The World,"['china', 'world', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['China', 'China', 'China', 'China', 'China']"
Teacher Trying To Enjoy Summer But Also Worried About What S Going To Happen In The Fall,['teachers'],['B-VIC'],[],[]
Congratulatios You Have Won Mant K Free Trip To China,['china'],['B-VIL'],"['MISC', 'LOC']","['Mant K', 'China']"
His Brain No His Hea Bid N President,['joe biden'],['B-HERO'],[],[]
Coronavirus Spread Me Realizing My Shirt Is Made In China Get This Shit Off Me,"['china', 't shirt', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China']"
This Virus Could Be With U For Quite Awhile Iexpect It To Start To Clear Out The Day After The Election,"['election', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Class Of 2021 Making Meme On Class Of 2020 Having An Online Graduation Class Of 2021 Realizing They Might Have An Entire Year Online Made With Mematie,"['class of 2020', 'class of 2021']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Why Get The China Virus When You Could Get A Case Of Corona No I Said I Have A Case Of Corona 12 You Said You Were Sick Corona Extra Corom Ea Cut Paste Sphotos Alip Com 6 52 Am 3 10 20 Twitter For Iphone,"['coronavirus', 'chinavirus', 'china virus', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['China Virus', 'Corona', 'Corona', 'Iphone']"
The Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu Lcom Haching Hachong Anarcho Memecapistan,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'chinavirus', 'kung flu', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu', 'Lcom Haching Hachong Anarcho Memecapistan']"
Other News France Macron Urge People To Limit Visit To Elderly,['emmanuel macron'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'ORG']","['France', 'Macron']"
Medium Why Do You Keep Calling It The Chinese Virus Trump Because It Came From China,"['china', 'donald trump', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Chinese Virus', 'Trump', 'China']"
Leaked Footage Of Japan Preparing For Www3,"['ww3', 'world war 3', 'japan']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['Japan']
Stock Up Food For Corona Clean Pantry For Passover,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'MISC']","['Corona', 'Passover']"
Me Reading The Seventh Email About School Opening Contradicting The Last Six Email What,"['school', 'emails']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Tchill Out Have A Corona Caron,"['corona beer', 'corona']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Corona Caron']
Whole World Is Blaming Chinese For Eatinganything And Spreading Corona Bear Grylls Starecat Com,"['bear grylls', 'chinese', 'coronavirus', 'corona']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG']","['Whole World', 'Chinese', 'Corona', 'Bear Grylls Starecat Com']"
Congrats To The Corona Virus For Being The First Thing Made In China To Last Longer Than A Month Starecat Com,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Corona Virus', 'China', 'Starecat Com']"
Donald J Trump Arody Donaldjtrummp China Want Their Name On Everything But This Virus 3 25 Pm 3 19 20 Twitter For Iphone,"['china', 'donald trump', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG', 'PER', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Donald J Trump', 'Arody', 'Donaldjtrummp', 'China', 'Iphone']"
The British Government S Changing Coronavirus Advice Stay At Home Alert,"['british government', 'uk government', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['British']
Plague Start In China First Confirmed Case In U The Guy At Area 51 Playing Plague Inc,"['china', 'usa', 'plague', 'area 51', 'us']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['China', 'U', 'Area 51', 'Inc']"
When You See A Chinese Dude Sneezing At The Airport,"['airport', 'chinese', 'chinese dude']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chinese']
Me Last Year When A Student Wanted To Give Me A Hug Awwww Come Here Honey You Re So Sweet Me When Student Want To Hug Me Now Teachertrauma Don T Touch Me,"['students', 'student']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Chinese Product Chinese Virus,"['chinese products', 'china', 'coronavirus', 'tony stark', 'chunky pandey', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese', 'Chinese']"
Corona Virus Will Not Last Long Openin Man Tut Thue Fri Sat Sunday Becase It Made In China Makeameme Org Emefka Sk,"['made in china', 'china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Corona Virus', 'China', 'Org', 'Emefka Sk']"
For My Next Trick I Ll Make Libtards Defend China For Hiding Information About The Chinese Virus And Saying It Racist To Call It Chinese Virus Makeameme Org,"['china', 'libtards', 'donald trump', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Chinese Virus', 'Chinese Virus']"
James Feitono Me The Very Second Rve Taken My Vaccine 2 5 M Mov 2020 O9 1K Boredpanda Com,"['vaccine', 'covid vaccine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'ORG']","['James Feitono', 'Com']"
No Traffic On 14 Yes What Did It Cost Everything,['i4'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Yadi Isko Corona Virus Ho Jaye Toh Ye China Walon Ki Poori Ankhen Khol Dega O,"['china', 'kim jong un', 'coronavirus', 'kim jong un']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Yadi Isko Corona Virus', 'Ho', 'Toh', 'China Walon Ki Poori', 'Khol Dega']"
When You Are A Usefull Method To Introduce The New World Order Deon,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'PER']","['New World Order', 'Deon']"
Congrats To The Corona Virus For Being The First Thing Made In China To Last Longer Than A Month,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Corona Virus', 'China']"
I D Like To Cancel My Subscription To 2021 I Ve Experienced The Free 7 Day Trial And L M Not Interested,['2021'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Rose Are Red April Is Grey The Next Time You Leave Your House,[],[],[],[]
When You Leave Your Family To Go And Get Supply,[],[],[],[]
Wuhan Virus You Re Racist Then Why Do You Use It S Racist To Use Spanish Flu Wuhan Virus What About I Said It S Racist To Use Wuhan Virus German Measles You Are Double Standard Racismmmm,"['wuhan virus', 'spanish flu', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'german measles']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan Virus', 'Spanish Flu', 'Wuhan Virus', 'Wuhan Virus', 'German Measles']"
The Real Pandemic Is Child Sex Trafficking,"['child sex trafficking', 'children', 'pandemic']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Pandemic', 'Child Sex Trafficking']"
Extraterrestrial Norway Go Back To The Playa Yuppie Scum 375 Glassr Highway Flynite Rebel Scifli Dc Walla Nalla Onel,[],[],"['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Extraterrestrial', 'Norway', 'Playa', 'Highway', 'Walla Nalla']"
Corona Virus Is A Dangerous Virus That Can Kill Easley Chinese Eats It Anyway The Virus The Chinese Virus Can Eat Everything,"['chinese', 'chinese virus', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Corona Virus', 'Easley', 'Chinese Eats', 'Chinese Virus']"
Product Made In China Virus Made In China,"['china', 'chinese product', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC']","['China', 'China']"
Coronavirus Testing New Option For Consumer Screening Website Log In And Symptom Screening Tool Yes No Symptom No Symptom Drive Thru Testing Clinic Of The Lab Test Shipped To Lab Result Displayed On Screening Website State Seal Of United Of The Preside,"['donald trump', 'covid19 patients', 'coronavirus', 'us government']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
How A Guy Eating Bat Soup In China Led To A Toilet Paper Shortage In The U,"['china', 'usa', 'bat soup', 'us', 'toilet paper']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Bat Soup', 'China', 'U']"
Other Country Have Normal Health And Food Regulation That Keep The Public Safe From Infectious And Potentially Deadly Disease China Bat Soup,"['china', 'bat soup', 'other countries']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['China', 'Bat Soup']"
Product Package Said Face Mask Thefunnybeaver Com,['face mask'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Thefunnybeaver Com']
I Just Want To Say One Thing About Coronavirus This Is The Longest Something Made In China Ha Ever Lasted,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China']"
Han Ia Mad Canned Laughter Unavailable,[],[],"['PER', 'MISC']","['Han Ia', 'Laughter']"
Kid Hey Mum When Is This Corona Virus Thing Gon Na Be Over Mum Just Shut Up And Eat Your Toilet Paper Er,"['coronavirus', 'kid', 'toilet paper']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Corona Virus']
When You Re The Doctor But Hc News The Village Idiot Is Giving Medical Advice Makeameme Org,"['donald trump', 'dr  anthony fauci', 'dr  anthoy fauci']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Hc', 'Village Idiot', 'Org']"
Working From Home With No Access To Deskphone Instagram Oitovip,[],[],"['ORG', 'ORG']","['Deskphone', 'Oitovip']"
Work From Home Expectation Reality 371,['work from home'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Covid 19 Doesn T Affect The Young You Re Not Young Anymore Boredpanda Com,"['covid19', 'covid 19']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG']","['Covid', 'Com']"
I M Not A Regular Mom Iima Cool Mom Quickn,[],[],['ORG'],['Iima']
Store In China When All There Customer Die Of A Virus Not Stonks 3510 26 1 550 0 12 Made This After Some Guy Made A Post Begging People To Stop Making China Virus Meme,"['stores in china', 'china', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC']","['China', 'China']"
When You Realize People Under 21 Legally Can T Get The Corona Virus 3 34 I Am Above The Law 14K View O 7 Year Ago,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Corona']
Covid 19 Got U All Like Karen Come Look At All The Wine Bottle In Linda S Recycling Bin,"['covid19', 'karens']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'LOC']","['Covid', 'Linda S']"
With The Lockdown You Will Have Some Time To Rest I Work In Cybersecurity,"['cybersecurity people', 'cybersecurity']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Corona Beer Change Their Name To Avoid Association With The Corona Virus Outbreak Eb Ebol Ehola Ebola Extra Extre,"['corona beer', 'ebola extra', 'ebola', 'coronavirus', 'corona']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Corona Beer', 'Corona', 'Ebol Ehola', 'Ebola']"
Hollywood Exposed Andstuffl I M Just A Girl Standing 6 Foot Away From A Boy Asking Him To Maybe Move Back Another Foot Thanks Socialdistancingpickuplines Ard O 8 774 2 56 Am Mar 20 2020 2 037 People Are Talking About This,['hollywood exposed'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Hollywood']
You Ha To Work From Home Dis Month Oh Darn O Instagram Johandahm,['work from home'],['B-OTH'],"['PER', 'PER']","['You Ha', 'Johandahm']"
Mr President They Re Saying Calling It The Wuhan Virus Is Racist Hold My Diet Coke The Chinese Virus,"['donald trump', 'wuhan virus', 'china', 'diet coke', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan Virus', 'Chinese Virus']"
Let Me Be Clear I Igned The Medical Appliance Tax Bill That Forced Company To Outsource Manufactoring Of Mask Gown Glove And Ventilaors To China Europe And Russia To Avoid The Tax,"['barack obama', 'china', 'mask', 'companies', 'gloves', 'europe', 'russia']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Mask Gown', 'China', 'Europe', 'Russia']"
Taipei Time Horme Front Page Sat Aug 29 2020 Paget China Arrest 12 Reportedly Fleeing To Taiwan You Cant Jast Lave Cina So Talwan Isn T Witheut Pemissien Part Of China Il Ii,"['china', 'tiwan', 'taiwan']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG']","['Taipei', 'Time', 'China', 'Taiwan', 'Cina', 'Witheut Pemissien', 'China', 'Il Ii']"
In The Case Of The Coronavirus Lii China You Are The Father,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus Lii', 'China']"
Coronavirus How To Wash Your Hand 1 Gently Wipe Each Finger With A Tiny Wet Cloth For 1 Second Turn On The Water With Your Mouth So Your Dirty Hand Dont Touch The Tap 3 Use Your Teeth To Remove Any Dirt From Under Your Fingernail That You Might Have Missed Dry Your Clean Hand On A Child Hair,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
When I See A Chinese Boy Coughing Me Killthe Virus,"['chinese', 'chinese boy', 'virus', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chinese']
After Listening To Linda His Human For 12 Day While In Quarantine A She Complained For Hour On End Sparky Realized He Wa Not Cut Out To Be An Emotional Support Dog Imgfip Com,"['dog', 'quarantine', 'sparky', 'human', 'linda']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER', 'ORG']","['Linda', 'Sparky', 'Imgfip Com']"
The White Washingt Aaren Rapar Atrupar Reporter Why Do You Keep Calling The Coronavirus The Chinese Virus There Are Report Of Violence Against Asian American Trump It Come From China That S Why,"['donald trump', 'china', 'asian americans', 'reporter', 'coronavirus', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PER', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['The', 'Washingt', 'Aaren', 'Rapar', 'Atrupar', 'Coronavirus', 'Chinese', 'Asian American', 'China']"
This Chinese Virus If Trump Insists On Calling It The Chinese Virus Should We Start Calling Maga Hat Chinese Hat That S Where The Come From After All Erica Again,"['donald trump', 'china', 'maga hats', 'chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese Virus', 'Trump', 'Chinese Virus', 'Maga Hat', 'Chinese Hat']"
The E E Ngto It Come Om Chi Na,"['donald trump', 'china']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Chi']
If You Could At Least Pretend To Work From Home That Would Be Great,['work from home'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
When You Find Out Your Normal Daily Lifestyle Is Called Quarantine,['quarantine'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
People Of Delhi Earthquake Corona Virus,"['earthquake', 'coronavirus', 'people of delhi']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIC']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['People', 'Of Delhi Earthquake', 'Corona Virus']"
Detirae Desiraes Trump Say The Virus Is Fake Covid And I Took That Personally,"['donald trump', 'covid19', 'covid', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Trump', 'Covid']"
China Stop Eating Everything That Move,['china'],['B-VIL'],['LOC'],['China']
There Is A Much More Sinister Reason Why China Let The Virus Go And Withheld Information A Pelosi Said China Prefers Biden To Win The Election Where S Hunter Will Hunter Be Suicided Like Epstein Ndio Com,"['hunter biden', 'china', 'joe biden', 'jeffrey epstein', 'nancy pelosi']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'ORG']","['China', 'A', 'Pelosi', 'China', 'Biden', 'Hunter', 'Epstein Ndio Com']"
Are You Worried About The Coronavirus Nah It Won T Last Much Longer It S Made In China,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Coronavirus', 'China']"
Coronavirus Is China Virus E Enre,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Coronavirus Is', 'China']"
A New Lethal Virus Start Spreading Africa Nol What Sorry Force Of Habit China No,"['china', 'africa', 'who', 'coronavirus', 'world health organisation', 'world health organization  who ']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'LOC']","['Africa', 'China']"
Kkyoin Just Gon Na Start Killing People I Dont Find Funny Cthuluguu National Suicide Prevention Lifeline 1 800 273 8255 Medium Small Large Oof Size,"['national suicide', 'national suicide prevention lifeline']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Kkyoin', 'Cthuluguu', 'National Suicide Prevention Lifeline']"
Pete Allison Epete Alison Took That Government Career Test Looking Forward To My Pandemic Proof Career A A Check Note Oh For F Cinema Proiectionist Cinema Projectionist Operate The Equipment That Show Film In Cinema Average Salary E12 000 22 000 Starter Experienced 7 52 Pm Oct 7 2020,"['pandemic', 'government', 'cinema projectionist']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Pete Allison Epete', 'Alison']"
When You Ve Got A 98 Chance Of Surviving The China Virus Msm Just Get In The Coffin Visit Patriotpost U For The Best Humor And Meme,"['main stream media  msm ', 'mainstream media', 'people', 'coronavirus', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG']","['China Virus', 'Patriotpost']"
I Wa Going To Make A Joke About The Chinese Wuhan Virus But You Probably Will Not Get It,"['chinese wuhan virus', 'wuhan coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese', 'Wuhan Virus']"
Ok Who Ever Did This You Re A Legend Cutene My Precios Customer Notice Horednond,['toilet paper'],['B-OTH'],"['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Ok', 'Cutene', 'Precios', 'Horednond']"
Kristamartleeaor 1 The Corona Virus Won T Last Long Have A Referral For Some Buyer Fying In Next Week From Mainland China Because It Wa 2019 2020 Made In China,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC']","['Kristamartleeaor', 'Corona Virus', 'Mainland China', 'China']"
The Corona Virus Won T Last Long Because It Wasmade In China,"['barack obama', 'china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Corona Virus', 'China']"
You Might Want To Cool It By Calling It The Chinese Virus Some People Might Think You Re A Racist Makeameme Org,"['chinese virus', 'china virus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese Virus', 'Racist Makeameme Org']"
The Picture You See Is A New Virus Discovered In Africa Called Human Papilloma Virus H I P Which Is Worst Than H L V One Could Be Affected With It Through Sex Even With The Use Of Condom Becouse Condom Can Do 60 Interms Of Protection So My Dear Be Careful And Forward It To Every Body You Care For,"['human papilloma virus', 'hip', 'hiv', 'africa', 'human papillomavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['LOC', 'MISC']","['Africa', 'Human Papilloma']"
Scientist Confirm Coronavirus Can Live Outside The Body For 7 Day Daty Of Rwo Infsenza A Hini Vanus Steains To Persist Ttarious Emironmental Condinonm H Demonstrated H Infectious On Stanless Steel Surface For 7 Day Addit Air Freight Wuhan To Sydney Transit Time Daya 5 7Days Australian Fuck,"['australians', 'coronavirus', 'h1n1 virus', 'scientists', 'wuhan', 'sydney']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Coronavirus', 'Rwo', 'Hini', 'Stanless Steel', 'Wuhan', 'Sydney', 'Australian']"
Republican Party Of Rock County Lighten Up Why Biden No Get Virus He Sniff Everyone D 20 1 Comment 6 Share Comment A Share,"['joe biden', 'donald trump', 'kim jong un', 'coronavirus', 'kim jong un', 'virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'PER', 'PER']","['Republican Party Of Rock County', 'Why', 'Biden']"
Exclusive Look At My Quarantine Hair,['quarantine'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Did You Know You Can Choke On A Carrot For Your Safety Have A Donut Dreomstime Com,['donut'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
What If March Really Ha 32 Day And April 1St Is Just A Prank,[],[],[],[]
When The Current Plague Isn T Your Fault,['plague'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Golf The Adult Version Of An Easter Egg Hunt,"['golf', 'easter egg hunt']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Golf', 'Easter Egg Hunt']"
A Few Week In Isolation With The Family What Could Go Wrong,[],[],[],[]
The 13Th 13Th 2020,[],[],[],[]
I M Just Se Stared Of Hig Ampty Dark Space A Void Good Advice Thank You,[],[],[],[]
Rep Mary Franson O Re 3 18 20 We Get It The Chinesevirus Could Have Been Controlled If China Had Been Honest Meanwhile People Are Hurting And In Mn It S Only Been One Day Of Business Being Shut Down What Is Being Done To Help People Don T Tell Me Unemployment Many Don T Qualify Quarantinelife O 16 O 21,"['china', 'people', 'quarantine', 'minnesota', 'china virus', 'mary franson']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Mary Franson', 'Chinesevirus', 'China']"
Me Realizing We Can Still Partyin Quarantine,['quarantine'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Deadly Wuhan Virus Speculated To Originate From Bat Soup,"['wuhan virus', 'bat soup', 'wuhan coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Wuhan Virus', 'Bat Soup']"
Me And The Boy Me And The Boy Headed To The Chinese Buffet Sad Newark,['chinese buffet'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'LOC']","['Chinese Buffet', 'Newark']"
Laughing At Corona Virus Meme When It Wa In China,"['china', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Corona Virus', 'China']"
When You Hear Your Neighbour Cough But Then You Smell Weed,"['neighbour', 'weed', 'cough']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Seriously Jolle Pape Tole Pape Joile Paper Pa,['toilet paper'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Pert Say Beady Whan Can Dty Akohol Gh Teimpeas Bar In China Be Like Thefunnybeaver Com Scann,"['alcohol', 'wuhan virus', 'china', 'bars', 'coronavirus', 'corona', 'corona beer']","['B-HERO', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC']","['Pert', 'Whan', 'Bar', 'China']"
Pro Of Social Distancing Never Shaving My Leg Again Wine Is Good For Your Heart Right Finally Have Time To Read A Book Even Though I Won T Bosbs Are Hanging Free Saving Money On Makeup,['social distancing'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
I Washed My Hand So Much Due To Codvid19 That My Exam Note From 1995 Resurfaced,"['covid19', 'hand wash', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Human Dang I Need To Self Quarantine For 2 Week Their Dog,"['dogs', 'humans', 'quarantine']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Corona Virus Virus Made In China Made In Chini Can Be Killed By Product Alcohol Adult Kid Top Funny Corona Meme,"['china', 'alcohol', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['Corona Virus', 'China', 'Chini', 'Corona']"
Me And The Squad Tryna Catch The Corona Virus So We Can Skip Work,"['corona beer', 'coronavirus', 'corona']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC']","['Me', 'Squad', 'Corona Virus']"
101 Year Old Man Who Survived Spanish Flu And World War 2 Now Beat Coronavirus Too Finallya Worthy Opponenti Our Battle Will Be Legendary,"['queen elizabeth', 'coronavirus', 'queen', 'spanish flu', 'world war 2']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Spanish Flu', 'World War 2', 'Coronavirus']"
People Who Made The Resolution About Travelling In 2020 Hewyude On Je N,"['people', 'people travelling in 2020', '2020']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Hewyude']
Ww3 Meme Corona Virus Meme Made In China So Won T Last Long Anyways,"['ww3', 'china', 'world war 3', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
When My Roomate Who Just Came Back From Visiting Family In China Tell Me She S Feeling A Bit Sick,['china'],['B-VIL'],['LOC'],['China']
Game Of Throne Coron Edition,"['game of thrones', 'coronavirus', 'toilet paper']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Game Of Throne Coron']
Thefunnybeaver Com Do Yau Know How Fast You Were Going Yes Sorry I Have Corona Virus Ok Carry On,"['coronavirus', 'police']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC']","['Com Do Yau', 'Corona']"
Callgomo Dowa The Eth Of The Trump Administration Extire B Populaton Why Would China Do This,"['donald trump', 'us population', 'donald trump administration', 'china']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC']","['Callgomo', 'Dowa', 'Trump Administration', 'China']"
World Coronavirus China Virus,"['china virus', 'china', 'world', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['World Coronavirus China']
Ram China Ke Muh Me Keede Pade Shyam Baddua Do Bhai Aashirwad Nai,['china'],['B-OTH'],"['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC']","['Ram China Ke', 'Baddua', 'Bhai Aashirwad']"
When Someonesneezes Under Quarntine,['quarantine'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
Let S See Who S Really Behind Coronavirus,['coronavirus'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
Indetode Education Pe A Eri Don T Try To Write This Project The Day Before Submission Challenge Accepted,[],[],"['ORG', 'ORG']","['Indetode Education', 'A Eri']"
Coming This Summer To A Yard Sale Near You,['toilet paper'],['B-OTH'],[],[]
China Virus Is A Joke Makeamenearg,"['donald trump', 'china virus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH']",['LOC'],['China']
Chinese Exchange Student Who Bought Corona Virus In The School,"['chinese exchange students', 'school', 'coronavirus', 'chinese student']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese', 'Corona']"
Saving The World In 1945 Saving The World In 2020,[],[],"['MISC', 'MISC']","['Saving The World', 'Saving The World']"
D Tiktok Oeyes Johnson When I Realize My Shirt Wa Made In China And China Ha The Coronavirus,"['china', 'shirt', 'tiktok', 'coronavirus']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC']","['D Tiktok Oeyes Johnson', 'China', 'China', 'Coronavirus']"
Otark Sinatra 2Nd Wave Of Coronavirus State Reopening Too Soon,"['states opening too soon', 'second wave of coronavirus', 'states', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'MISC']","['Otark Sinatra', 'Coronavirus']"
Friday The 13Th Friday The 13Th 2020 Made With Manatic,[],[],[],[]
When Your Friend Order A Mask For Corona Virus Protection But It Wa Shipped From China,"['china', 'mask', 'coronavirus']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'LOC']","['Corona', 'China']"
Can T Keep Virus Out Of Window 10 Want His Company To Develop The Vaccine For The Wuhan Virus,"['bill gates', 'wuhan virus', 'vaccine', 'wuhan coronavirus', 'windows 10']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Wuhan Virus']
My Bos Turned Herself Into A Potato On Our Microsoft Team Meeting And Can T Figure Out How To Turn The Setting Off So She Wa Just Stuck Like This The Entire Meeting,"['microsoft meeting', 'microsoft teams']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['ORG'],['Microsoft']
Why Aren T There Handle On Door Aymore Wesley It S Time I Tell You About The Year 2020 Boredpanda Com,[],[],"['PER', 'ORG']","['Aymore Wesley', 'Boredpanda Com']"
English Teacher Waiting For School To Reapen So They Can Give Write About Your Quar Ntine Day In 300 Word Essay A An Assignment School Finally Open After Covid19 Student During Exam,"['covid19', 'school', 'students', 'teachers']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",[],[]
Me Scrolling Through Instagram Finding Meme Relating To My Irrational Fear And Anxiety Blucyontheground A Umor Besed On My Pain Ah Ha Ha,['instagram'],['B-OTH'],['MISC'],['Instagram']
Barn Find All Original No Low Ball Offer I Know What I Have,['toilet paper'],['B-OTH'],['ORG'],['Barn']
Democrat It Is President Trump S Fault For The Spread Of The Corona Virus Hi I Am Xi Jinping Communist Leader Of China I Hid The Outbreak Of The Virus And Censored The Information In The World S Most Populated Country,"['xi jinping', 'donald trump', 'china', 'coronavirus', 'democrats']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'LOC']","['Democrat', 'Trump', 'Corona Virus', 'Xi Jinping', 'China']"
Corona Virus High Quality Mask Anti Bacteria Corona Virus Mouth Face Mask Brand New Unbranded 7 55 8 90 Free Shipping From China 9 86 D 12 151 63 Stonks Strricalcon,"['china', 'coronavirus', 'coronavirus', 'mask', 'face mask']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Corona Virus', 'Bacteria Corona Virus', 'Free', 'China', 'D', 'Stonks Strricalcon']"
When You Thought You Caught The Corona Virus B T The Doctor Say It S Just Cancer,"['coronavirus', 'doctor', 'cancer']","['B-VIL', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']",['MISC'],['Corona Virus']
The Apocalypse What I Expected What I Get O Anarchy Zombie Homedffice No Toilet Paper,"['the apocalypse', 'apocalypse', 'toilet paper', 'work from home']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['The Apocalypse', 'O Anarchy Zombie']"
Chinese Exchange Student Who Bought Corona Virus In The School,"['chinese exchange students', 'school', 'coronavirus', 'chinese student']","['B-VIL', 'B-VIC', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['MISC', 'MISC']","['Chinese', 'Corona']"
Beijing Biden I Mean You Know They Re Not Bad Folk Folk But Guess What They Re Not They Re Not Competition For U Joe Biden,"['china', 'beijing biden', 'joe biden', 'beijing']","['B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['PER', 'PER']","['Beijing Biden', 'Joe Biden']"
Swiggy Beme Detery Sere Cempany Zomato I Said Best Perfect,"['sonu sood', 'zomato', 'swiggy']","['B-HERO', 'B-OTH', 'B-OTH']","['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG', 'ORG']","['Swiggy', 'Beme', 'Sere Cempany Zomato', 'Said']"
