  Bernie Sanders    Elizabeth Warren  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Bernie Sanders', 'Elizabeth Warren']
  Uk Government  ,['ORG'],['Uk Government']
  Thais    Hong Kong  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['Thais', 'Hong Kong']
  China    Face Mask    Made In China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Face Mask', 'China']
  Joe Biden    Bernie Sanders    Kamala Harris    Tiktok  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Bernie Sanders', 'Kamala Harris', 'Tiktok']
  Donald Trump        Victoria Secret Store    Melania Trump    Victoria Secrets  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Victoria Secret Store', 'Melania', 'Trump', 'Victoria Secrets']
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Halloween  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama']
  China    People    World    Hantavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'People World Hantavirus']
  China    Plague    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['China Plague Coronavirus']
  Wuhan Coronavirus    China    Chinese New Year    Coronavirus    Chinese  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan', 'Coronavirus', 'China', 'Chinese New Year Coronavirus', 'Chinese']
  Hanta Virus    Coronavirus    Hantavirus    China  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['Hanta Virus Coronavirus', 'Hantavirus', 'China']
  Dr Grayfang    Quarantine  ,['LOC'],['Grayfang']
  Bubonic Plague    People    China    Swine Flu    Corona Swine Flu    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Bubonic Plague People', 'China Swine Flu Corona Swine Flu Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Great Wall Of China    China    Mexicans    Wall  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Great Wall Of China', 'China', 'Mexicans Wall']
  China    Karens    Plague    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Karens Plague Coronavirus']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Donald Trump    China    Reporter    Coronavirus    Chinese Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump China Reporter', 'Coronavirus', 'Chinese Virus']
  Jared Leto    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Jared Leto Coronavirus']
  Chinese Student    Coughing Chinese Student    Chinese Students  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'Chinese', 'Chinese']
  Internet Explorer    China    Breaking News    Coronavirus    New Virus In China  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['Internet Explorer China', 'Coronavirus', 'China']
  Coronavirus    China  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['Coronavirus', 'China']
  Bikers    Coronavirus    Gloves    Face Mask    Isolation  ,[],[]
  China    Coronavirus    Chinese    Chinese Coronavirus    Kung Flu  ,['MISC'],['China Coronavirus Chinese Chinese Coronavirus Kung Flu']
  Us Population    Us Government    Government  ,[],[]
  China    Trip To China  ,['LOC', 'LOC'],['China', 'China']
  Donald Trump    Chelsea Clinton    Lars Printzen    Cnn    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Chelsea Clinton', 'Lars Printzen', 'Cnn Coronavirus']
  Politicians    Coronavirus    Covid Facts    Us Population  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Covid']
  Joe Biden    Hunter Biden    Covid19  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Hunter Biden Covid19']
  China    Workers  ,['ORG'],['China Workers']
  Funny Mask    Face Mask    Orange  ,['MISC'],['Funny Mask']
  Norwegian Poker Translator  ,['MISC'],['Norwegian']
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump']
  Communist    China    Russia  ,['LOC', 'LOC'],['Communist China', 'Russia']
  China    Coronavirus    Area 51    Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus Area 51']
  China    Swine Flu    New Swine Flu Like Virus    Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['China Swine Flu', 'New Swine Flu']
  Cholera Outbreak    Bubonic Plague    Plague    Coronavirus    Cholera  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Cholera', 'Bubonic Plague Plague', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Pumpkin  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Pumpkin']
  Dna    Virus    Experimental Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Dna Virus']
  Conservative    Liberal    Charlie Kirk    American    Usa  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Conservative', 'Liberal', 'Charlie Kirk', 'American']
  Pifzer    Work From Home    Pfizer  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Pifzer', 'Pfizer']
  Barack Obama    Baby  ,['PER'],['Barack Obama']
  Covid Vaccine    Covid Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Hanta Virus    Hantavirus    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Hanta Virus', 'Hantavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Mainstream Media    China    Media House    Chinese Communist Party    Media Houses  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Mainstream Media China Media House', 'Chinese Communist Party Media Houses']
  Covid Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Donald Trump    Dr  Anthony Fauci    White House    Nbc News  ,['PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'White House', 'Nbc News']
  Homeless People    Society  ,['ORG'],['Homeless People Society']
  Media    People    Coronavirus Vaccine    Cattle    Media House    Coronavirus    Mask    American    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Media House', 'Coronavirus', 'American Covid Vaccine']
  Introverts    China Virus  ,['MISC'],['China Virus']
  Kim Jong Un    Kim Jong Un    Coronavirus    Joe Biden    Kim Jong Un    Virus  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Kim Jong Un', 'Kim Jong Un Coronavirus', 'Joe Biden', 'Kim Jong Un Virus']
  Corona Beer    Corona  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Corona Beer', 'Corona']
  Plague  ,[],[]
  China    Online Gamers    Firewall  ,['MISC'],['China Online Gamers Firewall']
  Us Government    Coronavirus Patients    Covid19 Patients    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  China Virus    Spanish Flu    Spanish People  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Spanish Flu', 'Spanish']
  China    Hong Kong Protestors    Hong Kong    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Hong Kong', 'Hong Kong']
  Quaratine Food  ,[],[]
  Cat Meme    Pandemic    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Cat Meme Pandemic Coronavirus']
  China    China Wuhan Coronavirus    Coronavirus    Wuhan  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['China', 'China', 'Wuhan', 'Coronavirus Coronavirus', 'Wuhan']
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Pandemic    Cnn    Coronavirus    H1N1    H1N1 Flu  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama', 'Pandemic Cnn Coronavirus', 'Flu']
  Donald Trump    Zombie Bite  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Zombie Bite']
  China    Covid19    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['China', 'Covid19', 'China Virus']
  Barack Obama    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Joe Biden']
  China    Hong Kong    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Hong Kong', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    James Woods    James Wood  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'James Woods', 'James Wood']
  Government    People    Unemployement    Human Rights  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump    Coronavirus    H1N1  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump', 'Coronavirus']
  China    Tiktok    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Tiktok Coronavirus']
  Chef    Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Chef Vaccine']
  Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Right Wing    Right Wing  ,[],[]
  Pubg    Indian Parents  ,['MISC'],['Indian']
  Queen    The Queen    British  ,['MISC'],['British']
  Mask    Vaccine    Microchip  ,[],[]
  Harvey Weinstein    China Virus  ,['ORG'],['Harvey Weinstein China Virus']
  China    The World    Covid19    World  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'World Covid19']
  Coronavirus    Corona Extra    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Corona', 'Corona', 'Beer']
  Russian Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Russian']
  China Virus  ,['LOC'],['China']
  China    Covid19    Covid 19    Narendra Modi  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PER'],['China', 'Covid19', 'Covid', 'Narendra Modi']
  Andy Burnham    Boris Johnson  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Andy Burnham', 'Boris Johnson']
  Government Officials    Country    Vaccine    Government    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Covid']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Coronavirus    Abraham Lincoln    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Coronavirus', 'Abraham Lincoln', 'Joe Biden']
  Coronavirus    Tofu  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Tofu']
  Norton Antivirus Mask    Norton Antivirus Antivirus    Norton Antivirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Norton Antivirus Mask', 'Norton Antivirus Antivirus', 'Norton Antivirus']
  Vladimir Putin    Vaccine    World  ,['MISC'],['Vladimir Putin Vaccine World']
  China    New Disease    Plague  ,['MISC'],['China New Disease Plague']
  Boris Johnson    Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Boris', 'Johnson', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Rekha    Amitabh Bachchan    Coronavirus    Amitabh Bacchan    Amit Shah  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Rekha', 'Amitabh Bachchan', 'Coronavirus', 'Amitabh Bacchan', 'Amit Shah']
  Vaccine Phase 3 Trial    Vaccine    Chef  ,[],[]
  Hantavirus    China    Rodents    Hanta Virus    Chinese  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Hantavirus', 'China', 'Hanta Virus', 'Chinese']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Russian Scientists    Vaccine    Covid Vaccine    Coronavirus    Vladimir Putin    Russia    Vladimir Putin  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PER', 'LOC', 'PER'],['Russian', 'Vaccine', 'Covid', 'Vladimir Putin', 'Russia', 'Vladimir Putin']
  Tom Hanks    Covid Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Tom', 'Hanks', 'Covid Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Introverts    China    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'China']
  Covid Infected People    People With Normal Flu    People With Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid', 'Coronavirus']
  Tsingtao Beer    Corona Beer    Coronavirus    Tsingtao    Corona  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Tsingtao Beer', 'Corona Beer Coronavirus', 'Tsingtao Corona']
  Government Officials    Country    Covid Vaccine  ,[],[]
  Doctors    Covid Vaccine    Hydroxychloroquine    Covid Vaccine    Hydrochloroquine  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  China    Coronavirus    Reddit    Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus', 'Reddit']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Chinese Outbreak  ,['MISC'],['Chinese Outbreak']
  Twitter    Qanon  ,['PER'],['Qanon']
  Russian Vaccine    Russian Scientists    Russia Vaccine    Corona Vaccine    Vladimir Putin    Scientists    Russia    Research  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'LOC'],['Russian', 'Russian', 'Russia', 'Corona', 'Vladimir Putin', 'Russia']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Donald Trump    Coronavirus    Donald Trump  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Coronavirus', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  Plague    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Plague Coronavirus']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    China  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'China']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  China    Usa    Plague    Us  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['China', 'Usa Plague Us']
  Covidiots    Donald Trump    American People  ,['ORG', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Covidiots', 'Donald Trump', 'American People']
  Flu    Godzilla  ,['MISC'],['Flu Godzilla']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Russia    Coronavirus Vaccine    Usa    Vaccine    Us  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Russia', 'Coronavirus Vaccine']
  Thanos    Ponos  ,['ORG', 'PER'],['Thanos', 'Ponos']
  China    Wuhan    Donald Trump    Lei Meng Yan    Coronavirus    Whistleblower  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['China', 'Wuhan', 'Donald Trump', 'Lei', 'Yan']
  Donald Trump    Voters    Dr  Anthony Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Xi Jinping  ,['PER'],['Xi Jinping']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Lone Ranger  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Lone Ranger']
  Covid19    Usa    Mask    Kakashi    Kakashi Hatake    Us  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Usa', 'Mask Kakashi Kakashi Hatake']
  Extroverts    Introverts    Coronavirus    Mask    Hand Santitizer    Outbreak  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Kitten    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Kitten']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Mass Rapid Transit  Mrt   ,['ORG'],['Mass Rapid Transit']
  Toilet Papers    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Coronavirus    Usa  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus Usa']
  Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['ORG'],['Covid']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China    Tshirt    T Shirt  ,['ORG'],['China Tshirt']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Mjolnir    Captain America  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Mjolnir', 'Captain America']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Swede    Coronavirus    Corona  ,['MISC'],['Swede Coronavirus Corona']
  Cnn Reporter    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Cnn    Coronavirus    H1N1    H1N1 Flu  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama', 'Cnn Coronavirus']
  Quarantine Week  ,['MISC'],['Quarantine Week']
  Covid19    Dog    Dogs    Covid 19  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Dog', 'Covid']
  Melania Trump    Coronavirus    Face Mask    Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Melania', 'Trump', 'Coronavirus', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Donald Trump    China    Syphilis    China Virus    Trump Virus  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'China', 'Syphilis China', 'Trump Virus']
  Air Freshner    Students    Teacher    Teachers    Student  ,[],[]
  Indian Cook  ,['MISC'],['Indian Cook']
  Urrak    Sanitizer    Bernie Sanders    Soap    Handwash  ,['ORG', 'PER'],['Urrak', 'Bernie Sanders']
  Donald Trump    California    Covid19    Hazmat Suit    Tump Supporter    Mask    Donald Trump Supporter  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'California', 'Hazmat Suit', 'Donald Trump']
  Dr  Anthony Fauci    Anthony Fauci    Donald Trump    Valdimir Puitin    Mask    Vladimir Putin    Vladimir Putin  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Anthony Fauci', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Donald Trump', 'Valdimir Puitin', 'Vladimir Putin', 'Vladimir Putin']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  China    Joe Biden    Hunter Biden    Nancy Peloci    Jeffrey Epstein    Virus  ,['LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['China', 'Joe Biden', 'Hunter Biden', 'Nancy Peloci', 'Jeffrey Epstein']
  Doctor    Wuhan Virus    Doctors    Coronavirus    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Doctor Wuhan Virus Doctors', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona', 'Corona Beer']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  China    Wuhan People    Wuhan    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['China', 'Wuhan People', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  China    Usa    Coronavirus    Africa  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Usa Coronavirus', 'Africa']
  Doctor    Wuhan Virus    China    Coronavirus    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Doctor Wuhan Virus', 'China Coronavirus', 'Corona Corona Beer']
  Virus    Virologist    Bandana  ,['PER'],['Bandana']
  Wuhan Virus    Airport    Coronavirus    Chinese Woman    Wuhan    France    Travellers  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Wuhan Virus Airport', 'Chinese', 'Wuhan', 'France']
  Chinese    Mr Stark    Chinese Dude    Spiderman  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'Stark', 'Chinese Dude', 'Spiderman']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China    Chink Virus    Donald Trump  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['China', 'Chink Virus', 'Donald Trump']
  Muhammad Sarim Akhtar    Among Us  ,['PER'],['Muhammad Sarim Akhtar']
  Coronavirus    Lockdown    Democrats    People    United Nations    United Nations  Un   ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Coronavirus Lockdown', 'Democrats People United Nations United Nations Un']
  Chinese New Year    Relatives    Wuhan    Facebook  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['Chinese New Year', 'Wuhan']
  Made In China    China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'China Coronavirus']
  Aids    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Aids', 'Coronavirus China']
  China    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus', 'China Virus']
  Chinese People    Biohazard 8    Ps4  ,['ORG'],['Chinese People Biohazard']
  China    Plague    Disease    Virus  ,['MISC'],['China Plague Disease Virus']
  China    Cnn    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Cnn Coronavirus']
  Chinese Government    Usa    China    Covid 19 Cases    Covid19 Cases    Woman    Man  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Chinese', 'Usa China Covid', 'Covid19']
  Joe Biden    Bernie Sanders    Bernie Sanders    Kamala Harris  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Bernie Sanders', 'Bernie Sanders', 'Kamala Harris']
  Waffle House  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Waffle', 'House']
  China    Herald Newspaper    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['China Herald Newspaper', 'Coronavirus']
  Word Health Organisation    China    Africa    World Health Organization  Who   ,['ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG'],['Word Health Organisation', 'China', 'Africa', 'World Health Organization Who']
  China    Coronavirus    Baby  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus Baby']
  China    Coronavirus    Chinese Coronavirus    Kung Flu  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China Coronavirus', 'Chinese Coronavirus', 'Kung Flu']
  American Government    American Citizens    Usa Government    Us Government    Us Citizens    Citizens  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['American', 'American']
  Teachers  ,[],[]
  Protestors    Lockdown  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Campaign Rallies    Golf    Coronavirus    Public Health Experts  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump Campaign Rallies', 'Golf Coronavirus']
  China    Herald Newspaper    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['China Herald Newspaper', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Picture    Trevor Noah    The Daily Show    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Trevor Noah', 'The Daily Show', 'Coronavirus']
  Bernie Sanders    Pete Buttigieg  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Bernie Sanders', 'Pete Buttigieg']
  Weed    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Money Heist    Professor  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Lysol    Vaccine    Covid    Lisol    Lizol    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump Lysol Vaccine', 'Lisol Lizol', 'Vaccine']
  Us    Other Countries    Coronavirus    Usa  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Zoom    Covid19    China  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['Zoom Covid19', 'China']
  Parenting    Parents    Alcohol    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Alcohol Coronavirus']
  Bbc News  ,['ORG'],['Bbc News']
  Cigarette    Coronavirus    Mobile  ,['ORG'],['Cigarette Coronavirus']
  Teacher    Student  ,[],[]
  Vaccine    Texas    Flu Vaccine  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Texas', 'Flu']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Adolf Hitler  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Adolf Hitler']
  Usa    The World    Us    World  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Usa The World Us', 'World']
  Donald Trump    U S  Immigration And Customs Enforcement S  Ice     Mexicans    Ice Truck    Mexican Flag  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'U S Immigration And Customs Enforcement', 'S Ice Mexicans Ice Truck Mexican Flag']
  School    Kids    News  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['School', 'Kids', 'News']
  Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Covid19    Flu    Coronavirus    Mask    Cdc  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Centre For Disease Control', 'Coronavirus']
  Government  ,[],[]
  China    Joe Biden    Covid19    World    Coronavirus    Hunter Biden    Covid 19  ,['LOC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'ORG'],['China', 'Joe Biden', 'World Coronavirus Hunter', 'Biden', 'Covid']
  Government  ,[],[]
  Bandana    Virologists    Mask    Virus  ,['ORG'],['Bandana']
  Covid 19    Covid19  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid', 'Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Coronavirus    Mask    Cdc  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump Centre For Disease Control', 'Coronavirus Mask']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Student  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Tmz    Tmz News    Press  ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'News Press']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Mask Coronavirus']
  Media    Government    Media House    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Government Media House', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Alien  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Liberals        Donald Trump    Oxygen  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Liberals', 'Donald Trump']
  Coronavirus    Winchester  ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Coronavirus', 'Winchester']
  2020    Marty  ,['PER'],['Marty']
  Apocalypse Outfit  ,['ORG'],['Apocalypse Outfit']
  Donald Trump    Hillary Clinton    Mask  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Hillary Clinton']
  Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus    World Health Organization  Who   ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus', 'World Health Organization']
  Dr  Anthony Fauci    Donald Trump    Mask  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Anthony Fauci', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  Donald Trump    Reporter    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Coronavirus    Malaria  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Coronavirus']
  2020    Kobe Bryant    Country    Australia    Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Kobe Bryant', 'Country', 'Australia', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Mask    Hand Wash    The Guardian  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Mask Hand Wash', 'The Guardian']
  Us Government    Donald Trump    Usa  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    China    Chinese Virus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'China', 'Chinese Virus']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Donald Trump S Staff  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  Employee    Boss    Cid  ,['PER'],['Cid']
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Dr  Anthony Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump Covid19', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Coronavirus    2020  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus 2020']
  Us Navy    Us Citizens  ,['ORG'],['Navy']
  Social Distancing    Gondor  ,['LOC'],['Gondor']
  Afghanistan    Toilet Paper  ,['LOC'],['Afghanistan']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Mother Nature    Humanity    Wuhan Virus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Humans    Nature  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Klaus Schwab  ,['PER'],['Klaus Schwab']
  China    Wuhan Coronavirus    Mask    Wuhan  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Wuhan Coronavirus Mask', 'Wuhan']
  Donald Trump    China    Syphilis    China Virus    Trump Virus  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'China', 'Syphilis China', 'Trump Virus']
  Books  ,[],[]
  Wuhan Virus    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Scientists    Wuhan    Alcohol    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus Coronavirus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Wuhan Alcohol Corona Corona Beer']
  Uber Drivers    Uber    Government  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Uber', 'Uber']
  New York City    Mask    Ventilator    Brooklyn  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC'],['New York City', 'Mask Ventilator', 'Brooklyn']
  Football  ,[],[]
  Usa    Coronavirus    Nancy Pelosi    Cdc  ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Usa Coronavirus', 'Nancy Pelosi']
  Mask    God    Assault Rifle  ,['MISC'],['Mask God Assault Rifle']
  Youtube    White Guy    Chinese  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Youtube', 'White Guy', 'Chinese']
  Lifeguards    Government  ,[],[]
  Aliens  ,['MISC'],['Aliens']
  Wuhan Virus    Chinese Woman    Airport    Wuhan Coronavirus    France    Travellers  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan', 'Chinese Woman', 'Wuhan', 'France']
  Mother Nature    Humanity    Wuhan Virus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Humans    Nature  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Surgical Mask  ,[],[]
  Democrats    Covid19  ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Democrats', 'Covid19']
  Weed    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Teachers  ,[],[]
  Joe Biden    Mike Pence    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Coronavirus    People  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Mike Pence', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Plague    Plague Outbreak  ,['MISC'],['Plague Plague Outbreak']
  Thais    China    Hong Kong    Thailand  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Thais', 'China', 'Hong Kong', 'Thailand']
  Xi Jinping    Donald Trump    China    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Xi Jinping', 'Donald Trump', 'China Coronavirus China']
  Liberals    Left    Donald Trump  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Liberals', 'Donald Trump']
  Plague    Plague Outbreaks  ,[],[]
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Wuhan    Times Square    Carl Elemen  ,['LOC', 'PER'],['Wuhan Times Square', 'Carl Elemen']
  2020    People    Everyone    Kids  ,[],[]
  School    Kids    Homeschooled  ,[],[]
  Government    People  ,[],[]
  Ludo King  ,['PER'],['Ludo']
  Jumanji    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Jumanji Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Asian    China    Asian People    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Asian China Asian People Coronavirus']
  China    World    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'World Coronavirus']
  Teachers  ,[],[]
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Joe Biden  ,['PER'],['Joe Biden']
  China    T Shirt    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'T Shirt Coronavirus']
  Election    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Election Coronavirus']
  Class Of 2020    Class Of 2021  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Chinavirus    China Virus    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Chinavirus', 'China Virus', 'Corona Corona Beer']
  China    Coronavirus    Chinavirus    Kung Flu    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China Coronavirus', 'Chinavirus', 'Kung Flu China Virus']
  Emmanuel Macron  ,['PER'],['Emmanuel Macron']
  China    Donald Trump    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Donald Trump', 'Chinese Virus', 'China']
  Ww3    World War 3    Japan  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['World War', 'Japan']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  School    Emails  ,[],[]
  Corona Beer    Corona  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Corona Beer', 'Corona']
  Bear Grylls    Chinese    Coronavirus    Corona  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Bear Grylls', 'Chinese Coronavirus Corona']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  China    Donald Trump    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Donald Trump Coronavirus']
  British Government    Uk Government    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['British', 'Government', 'Uk Government', 'Coronavirus']
  China    Usa    Plague    Area 51    Us  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Usa', 'Plague Area']
  Airport    Chinese    Chinese Dude  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Airport', 'Chinese Chinese']
  Students    Student  ,[],[]
  Chinese Products    China    Coronavirus    Tony Stark    Chunky Pandey    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'China', 'Coronavirus', 'Tony Stark', 'Pandey', 'Chinese Virus', 'China']
  Made In China    China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'China Coronavirus']
  China    Libtards    Donald Trump    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Donald Trump', 'Chinese Virus', 'China Virus']
  Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['ORG'],['Covid']
  I4  ,[],[]
  China    Kim Jong Un    Coronavirus    Kim Jong Un  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Kim Jong Un Coronavirus', 'Kim Jong Un']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  2021  ,[],[]
  Wuhan Virus    Spanish Flu    Wuhan Coronavirus    German Measles  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'Spanish Flu', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'German Measles']
  Child Sex Trafficking    Children    Pandemic  ,['MISC'],['Child Sex Trafficking Children Pandemic']
  Chinese    Chinese Virus    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Chinese Chinese Virus Coronavirus', 'China', 'Virus']
  China    Chinese Product    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Chinese', 'China']
  Donald Trump    Covid19 Patients    Coronavirus    Us Government  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China    Usa    Bat Soup    Us    Toilet Paper  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['China', 'Usa Bat Soup']
  China    Bat Soup    Other Countries  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['China', 'Bat Soup']
  Face Mask  ,['MISC'],['Face Mask']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  China    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Chinese', 'China']
  Coronavirus    Kid    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Dr  Anthoy Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Anthoy Fauci']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Covid 19  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Covid']
  Stores In China    China    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'China', 'Coronavirus China']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Karens  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Karens']
  Cybersecurity People    Cybersecurity  ,[],[]
  Corona Beer    Ebola Extra    Ebola    Coronavirus    Corona  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Corona Beer', 'Ebola', 'Ebola', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona']
  Hollywood Exposed  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Hollywood', 'Exposed']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Wuhan Virus    China    Diet Coke    Wuhan Coronavirus    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Wuhan Virus China Diet Coke', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Chinese Virus', 'China']
  Barack Obama    China    Mask    Companies    Gloves    Europe    Russia  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'LOC'],['Barack Obama', 'China Mask Companies Gloves Europe', 'Russia']
  China    Tiwan    Taiwan  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Tiwan', 'Taiwan']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Chinese    Chinese Boy    Virus    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Chinese Chinese Boy Virus Coronavirus']
  Dog    Quarantine    Sparky    Human    Linda  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Sparky', 'Linda']
  Donald Trump    China    Asian Americans    Reporter    Coronavirus    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'China Asian Americans', 'Coronavirus', 'Chinese Virus', 'China Virus']
  Donald Trump    China    Maga Hats    Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'China', 'Maga Hats', 'Chinese Virus', 'China Virus']
  Donald Trump    China  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'China']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Earthquake    Coronavirus    People Of Delhi  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['People', 'Of Delhi']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Hunter Biden    China    Joe Biden    Jeffrey Epstein    Nancy Pelosi  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Hunter Biden', 'China', 'Joe Biden', 'Jeffrey Epstein', 'Nancy Pelosi']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  China    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus', 'China Virus']
  National Suicide    National Suicide Prevention Lifeline  ,['MISC'],['National Suicide National Suicide Prevention Lifeline']
  Pandemic    Government    Cinema Projectionist  ,['MISC'],['Pandemic']
  Main Stream Media  Msm     Mainstream Media    People    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['People', 'Coronavirus', 'China Virus']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Barack Obama    China    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'China', 'Coronavirus']
  Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'China']
  Human Papilloma Virus    Hip    Hiv    Africa    Human Papillomavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Human Papilloma Virus', 'Hiv', 'Africa', 'Human Papillomavirus']
  Australians    Coronavirus    H1N1 Virus    Scientists    Wuhan    Sydney  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Australians', 'Coronavirus H1N1', 'Wuhan', 'Sydney']
  Joe Biden    Donald Trump    Kim Jong Un    Coronavirus    Kim Jong Un    Virus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Joe Biden', 'Donald Trump', 'Kim Jong Un Coronavirus', 'Kim Jong Un Virus']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donut  ,[],[]
  Plague  ,[],[]
  Golf    Easter Egg Hunt  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Golf', 'Easter Egg Hunt']
  China    People    Quarantine    Minnesota    China Virus    Mary Franson  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'PER'],['China', 'People Quarantine Minnesota', 'China', 'Mary Franson']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Wuhan Virus    Bat Soup    Wuhan Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'Bat Soup', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Chinese Buffet  ,['MISC'],['Chinese Buffet']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Neighbour    Weed    Cough  ,['PER'],['Weed Cough']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Alcohol    Wuhan Virus    China    Bars    Coronavirus    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'China Bars', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona Corona Beer']
  Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Hand Wash    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Dogs    Humans    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  China    Alcohol    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Alcohol Coronavirus']
  Queen Elizabeth    Coronavirus    Queen    Spanish Flu    World War 2  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Queen Elizabeth Coronavirus Queen', 'Spanish Flu', 'World War 2']
  People    People Travelling In 2020    2020  ,[],[]
  Ww3    China    World War 3    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'World War 3', 'Coronavirus']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Game Of Thrones    Coronavirus    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Game Of Thrones']
  Coronavirus    Police  ,['ORG'],['Coronavirus Police']
  Donald Trump    Us Population    Donald Trump Administration    China  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'LOC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'China']
  China Virus    China    World    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Virus China World Coronavirus']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    China Virus  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'China']
  Chinese Exchange Students    School    Coronavirus    Chinese Student  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'Coronavirus', 'Chinese']
  China    Shirt    Tiktok    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['China Shirt Tiktok', 'Coronavirus']
  States Opening Too Soon    Second Wave Of Coronavirus    States    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Bill Gates    Wuhan Virus    Vaccine    Wuhan Coronavirus    Windows 10  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Bill', 'Gates', 'Wuhan Virus Vaccine', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Windows 10']
  Microsoft Meeting    Microsoft Teams  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Microsoft', 'Meeting', 'Microsoft', 'Teams']
  Covid19    School    Students    Teachers  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Instagram  ,['MISC'],['Instagram']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Xi Jinping    Donald Trump    China    Coronavirus    Democrats  ,['PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Xi Jinping', 'Donald Trump', 'China', 'Coronavirus Democrats']
  China    Coronavirus    Coronavirus    Mask    Face Mask  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Doctor    Cancer  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Doctor Cancer']
  The Apocalypse    Apocalypse    Toilet Paper    Work From Home  ,['MISC'],['The Apocalypse Apocalypse']
  Chinese Exchange Students    School    Coronavirus    Chinese Student  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'Coronavirus', 'Chinese']
  China    Beijing Biden    Joe Biden    Beijing  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'PER', 'LOC'],['China', 'Beijing', 'Biden', 'Joe Biden', 'Beijing']
  Sonu Sood    Zomato    Swiggy  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Sonu Sood', 'Zomato', 'Swiggy']
  Xi Jinping    China    Journalists    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Xi Jinping', 'China', 'Coronavirus', 'Wuhan', 'Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Work From Home  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Bill Gates    Viruses    Cnn    Windows 95    Virus    Bill   Melinda Gates Foundation  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Bill Gates Viruses Cnn', 'Windows 95', 'Bill', 'Melinda Gates Foundation']
  China    Coronavirus    People    Usa    Italy    Spain    Us  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Coronavirus People', 'Italy', 'Spain']
  China    Starbucks  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['China', 'Starbucks']
  Chian Virus    China Virus  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Chian', 'Virus', 'China', 'Virus']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Chinese Virus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'China']
  Hot Water    China    Coronavirus Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Hot Water China Coronavirus']
  Deanna Lorraine    Deanne Lorraine    Mask    Grand Old Party    God  ,['PER', 'PER', 'ORG'],['Deanna Lorraine', 'Deanne Lorraine', 'Grand Old Party']
  Us Population    Government  ,['ORG'],['Us']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  K L  Rahul    Rishabh Pant    Shikhar Dhawan    Rahul    Virat Kohli    Fans    Teammates    Dhawan    Pant  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['K L Rahul', 'Rishabh Pant', 'Shikhar Dhawan Rahul Virat Kohli', 'Dhawan Pant']
  Covid19    Quarantine    Snack Hoarding    Bikini Bodies    Covid 19  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Bikini Bodies']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Us Government    Media  ,['ORG'],['Us Government Media']
  Aids    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['Aids', 'China']
  Lockdown  ,[],[]
  Humans    The Earth    Aliens  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Humans', 'The', 'Earth', 'Aliens']
  Jenny    Tom Hanks    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Jenny Tom', 'Hanks', 'Coronavirus']
  Stock Market  ,[],[]
  2020    Travel Plans  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump    Cnn    Coronavirus    H1N1    H1N1 Flu  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump', 'Cnn Coronavirus']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Golf    Covid    Joe Biden    Scotland  ,['PER', 'PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Joe Biden', 'Scotland']
  Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Swine Flu    Election    Mers    Avian    Sars    Avian Flu    Zika    Ebola    Coronavirus    Corona    Election Year    Swine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Swine Flu', 'Avian Sars', 'Avian Flu', 'Zika', 'Ebola', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona', 'Swine']
  Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Corona Corona']
  Xi Jinping    Laxative  ,['PER'],['Xi Jinping']
  Umar Akmal  ,['PER'],['Umar Akmal']
  Purell    Ppe    School    Mask    Face Mask  ,['ORG'],['Purell Ppe School']
  Autism    Polio  ,['MISC'],['Autism Polio']
  Blood Cough    Dry Cough    Cough    Coronavirus  ,[],[]
  Work From Home    Pajamas  ,[],[]
  Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Kelis    Cdc    Kelis Rogers  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Centre For Disease Control', 'Kelis', 'Kelis Rogers']
  Royal Challengers Bangalore  Rcb     Royal Challangers Bangalore  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Royal Challengers Bangalore', 'Royal Challangers Bangalore']
  Donald Trump    2020    Covid19    Covid  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19', 'Covid']
  Socks    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump    Media    Swine Flu    Coronavirus    Joe Biden    H1N1    Bernie Sanders  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump', 'Swine Flu Coronavirus', 'Joe Biden', 'Bernie Sanders']
  Donald Trump    Stimulus Check    Voters    Election  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Dr  Anthoy Fauci    Covid19  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Anthoy Fauci Covid19']
  Boris Johnson  ,['PER'],['Boris Johnson']
  Donald Trump    Pandemic    Coronavirus    Democrats  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Pandemic Coronavirus', 'Democrats']
  American    Us    Mexico    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['American Us Mexico', 'Coronavirus']
  Memers    The World    World  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Memers', 'World World']
  Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Karen    Us    Usa    Karen Essential Oils    Coronavirus    Karens  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Karen Us', 'Karen Essential Oils Coronavirus', 'Karens']
  Covid19    Jamie    Covid  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Covid19', 'Jamie Covid']
  Dinosaur    Meteorite    Queen Elizabeth Ii    Queen    Queen Elizabeth  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Dinosaur Meteorite', 'Elizabeth Ii', 'Elizabeth']
  Elected Official    Canada    Postcard    International Travel    Elected Officials    Beach  ,['ORG'],['Canada Postcard International']
  Justin Trudeau    Canadians    Carbon Tax    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Justin Trudeau', 'Canadians Carbon Tax Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Dalgona Coffee    Burgers    Momos  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Dalgona Coffee', 'Burgers']
  Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Iran    Donald Trump  ,['LOC', 'PER'],['Iran', 'Donald Trump']
  Public    Mask    Walmart  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Public', 'Mask', 'Walmart']
  Disney World    Fun Spot America Theme Parks    Fun Spot    Seaworld    Universal Studios  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Disney World', 'Fun Spot', 'America Theme Parks', 'Spot', 'Seaworld', 'Universal Studios']
  Pandemic    Pizza  ,['MISC'],['Pandemic Pizza']
  Betty    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Betty Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    People  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Hand Sanitizer  ,[],[]
  Twitter    Donald Trump    Covid19    Covid  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Barack Obama    Toast  ,['PER'],['Barack Obama']
  Corona Beer    Ebola    Coronavirus    Corona  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Corona Beer', 'Ebola', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona']
  Hop Scotch Club    Hop Scotch    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Hop', 'Scotch Club', 'Scotch Coronavirus']
  Dwayne Johnson    Leonardo Dicaprio    Robert Downey Jr   ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Dwayne Johnson', 'Leonardo Dicaprio', 'Robert Downey Jr']
  Barack Obama  ,['PER'],['Barack Obama']
  China    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Coronavirus']
  Madagascar    Greenland    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Madagascar', 'Greenland Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Dr  Anthony Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Vicks Vaporub    Vicks    Covid19    Vicksvaporub  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Vicks Vaporub', 'Vicks Covid19', 'Vicksvaporub']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Immigration    American People    People Of Up    House  ,['MISC'],['American']
  Hillary Clinton    Joe Biden    Nancy Pelosi        Hillary Clinton    Demon  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Hillary Clinton', 'Joe Biden', 'Nancy Pelosi', 'Hillary Clinton', 'Demon']
  The World    Usa    Coronavirus    Rest Of The World    Us  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['The World Usa Coronavirus', 'Rest Of The World']
  American  ,['MISC'],['American']
  Covid19    Quarantine    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  The World  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['The', 'World']
  Shutdown    Lockdown  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Hospitals    Covid19    Ventilator  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Mask    Covid19    Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Mask    Fence    Chain Link Fence    Coronavirus    Microscopic Virus    Mosquito  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Us    Stay At Home    Corona Testing    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Donald Trump']
  Prince Charles    Queen    Kindergarten    Queen Elizabeth  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Charles', 'Elizabeth']
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump    China    Covid19    Coronavirus    H1N1    H1N1 Virus    H1N1 Flu  ,['PER', 'PER', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump', 'China', 'Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Covid19  ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Military Doctors    Experts    Ibuprofen    Coronavirus    France    Ibruprofen  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Ibuprofen', 'Coronavirus', 'France', 'Ibruprofen']
  Us Government    American    Africa  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['Us', 'American Africa']
  Barack Obama  ,['PER'],['Barack Obama']
  Coronavirus    Social Distancing  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Coronavirus    Chlamydia  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Chlamydia']
  Government  ,[],[]
  Media  ,[],[]
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Narendra Modi  ,['PER'],['Narendra Modi']
  Coronavirus    Ipl    Corona    Indian Premiere League    Rain  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Ipl', 'Corona', 'Indian Premiere League Rain']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Government    Mainstream Media    Main Stream Media  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Vaccine    People    Covid Vaccine    Mainstream Media  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Swine Flu    Election    Mers    Avian    Sars    Avian Flu    Zika    Plague    Ebola    Coronavirus    Corona    Election Year    Swine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Swine Flu', 'Avian Sars', 'Avian Flu', 'Zika', 'Ebola', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona', 'Swine']
  Coworkers    Meetings    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  April Fool S Day  ,['MISC'],['April Fool S Day']
  Mike Pence    Norton Antivirus    Coronavirus    Science  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Mike Pence', 'Norton', 'Antivirus', 'Coronavirus Science']
  Mexico    Coronavirus    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Mexico', 'Coronavirus', 'Corona Corona Beer']
  People Born In March  April  ,[],[]
  Virus  ,[],[]
  Horoscope  ,[],[]
  Pifzer    Moderna    Covid Vaccine  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Pifzer', 'Moderna', 'Covid', 'Vaccine']
  Anti Maskers  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Anti', 'Maskers']
  Coronavirus    Chinese Coronavirus    Kung Flu    China Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Chinese Coronavirus', 'Kung Flu', 'China Coronavirus']
  Batman    Bat    Robert Pattinson    Peter Sarsgaard    Bats    Pattinson  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Batman', 'Robert Pattinson', 'Peter Sarsgaard', 'Bats Pattinson']
  Who    Pandemic    Coronavirus    World Health Organization  Who   ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Who Pandemic Coronavirus', 'World Health Organization']
  High School  ,[],[]
  Telekinesis  ,['ORG'],['Telekinesis']
  Russian Vaccine    Coronavirus Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Russian Vaccine', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Grocery Store  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  California  ,['LOC'],['California']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Cake    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Cake Coronavirus']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Coronavirus    Covid  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Orange    Teacher    Teachers    Exam  ,['MISC'],['Orange']
  Admin    Teachers  ,[],[]
  Supermarket    Pandemic    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Chinese Food Place    Chinese  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese Food Place', 'Chinese']
  Diy Mask    Norton Antivirus    Mask    Anti Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Diy Mask Norton Antivirus Mask', 'Virus']
  Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    Kids    Mum  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Adam    Eve    God    Queen Elizabeth  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Adam', 'Eve', 'God', 'Elizabeth']
  Adam    Eve    Queen    Traffic    Teacher    Online Class    God  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Adam', 'Eve']
  Joe Biden    Covid19    Covid Vaccine  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Joe Biden', 'Covid19', 'Covid']
  Who    Pornhub Executives    Covid19    Quarantine    Coronavirus    Pornhub    World Health Organization  Who   ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Pornhub', 'World Health Organization']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Government    Scientist    People  ,[],[]
  Mexican Druglord Pablo Escobar    Pablo Escobar  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'PER'],['Mexican', 'Pablo Escobar', 'Pablo Escobar']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Military Doctors    Experts    Ibuprofen    Coronavirus    France    Ibruprofen  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Ibuprofen', 'Coronavirus', 'France', 'Ibruprofen']
  Black Mirror  ,['ORG'],['Black Mirror']
  Eggs    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Engineering    Engineering Students    Engineering People  ,[],[]
  Youtube    Professor  ,[],[]
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  King Lear    Sars    Rob Schneider    Quarantine    Plague    The Hot Chick    William Shakespeare  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['King Lear', 'Sars', 'Rob Schneider', 'Plague', 'Hot Chick', 'William Shakespeare']
  Mask    Vicks    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Mask Vicks Coronavirus']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Cough  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Beer    Sanitizer    Hand Sanitizer    Alcohol  ,[],[]
  Social Distancing    Friends  ,[],[]
  Pet    Family    Pets    Toilet Paper    Dogs    Savings  ,[],[]
  Cybersecurity People    Cybersecurity    Lockdown  ,['MISC'],['Cybersecurity']
  Chuck Norris    Quarantine    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Chuck Norris Quarantine Coronavirus']
  American    India    United States Of America  ,['LOC', 'LOC'],['American India', 'United States Of America']
  France    Covid19    Coronavirus    Smurfs  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['France', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus Smurfs']
  Quarantine    Narendra Modi  ,['PER'],['Narendra Modi']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Mask    Norton Antivirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Mask Norton', 'Antivirus']
  Quarantine Snacks    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Cloud  ,['PER'],['Cloud']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Parents    School    Schools  ,['ORG'],['Parents']
  Anglo Americans    Pubs    Coronavirus    Pub  ,['MISC'],['Anglo Americans']
  Tamilnadu    Coronavirus    Tamil Nadu  ,['MISC', 'LOC'],['Tamilnadu Coronavirus', 'Tamil Nadu']
  People    Covid19    Toilet Paper    South Korea    Korea  ,['LOC'],['South Korea Korea']
  Covid19    Quarantine    Toilet Paper    Doctor  ,[],[]
  Cgpa  ,['ORG'],['Cgpa']
  The World    Titanic  ,['MISC'],['The World Titanic']
  City Parents    Farm Parents    Coronavirus    School    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['City Parents Farm Parents', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Russian Vaccine    Russian Vodka  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Russian', 'Russian Vodka']
  Guy Eating A Bat    Bat  ,['MISC'],['Bat Bat']
  Universal Logo    Air Pollution    Sky    Universal Studios  ,['ORG'],['Universal Logo Air Pollution Sky Universal Studios']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Covid  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Covid']
  Dph    California    Usa    Coronavirus    Corona Testing  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['California', 'Usa', 'Coronavirus']
  Travelling People    Covid19    Covid 19  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Covid']
  Cat    Clown  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Cat', 'Clown']
  India Lockdown Announcement    India Lockdown Execution    Lockown    Lockdown In India    India  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['India', 'India', 'India', 'India']
  Santa Claus    Human Race    Covid19    Covid    Coronavirus    Christmas  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Santa Claus Human Race', 'Covid19', 'Covid Coronavirus Christmas']
  Covid19    Diego Maradona  ,['ORG', 'PER'],['Covid19', 'Diego Maradona']
  Twitter    Mexico    China    Virus  ,['LOC', 'LOC'],['Mexico', 'China']
  Car    Coffee Cup  ,['MISC'],['Car Coffee Cup']
  English Teachers    Quarantine    School    Teachers    Essay  ,['MISC'],['English']
  Karens    American    Mask  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Karens', 'American Mask']
  Family Of 6 Members    Austria    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Austria', 'Coronavirus']
  Soap    Hand Wash    Water  ,[],[]
  Hair  ,[],[]
  Polar Vortex    Cnn    American    American  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Polar Vortex', 'American American']
  Hand Soap  ,[],[]
  American  ,['MISC'],['American']
  Anthony Adams    Jehovah S Witnesses    Queen Elizabeth    Jehovah  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'PER'],['Anthony Adams', 'Jehovah S Witnesses', 'Elizabeth Jehovah']
  Amazon    Social Distancing    Outfit  ,['MISC'],['Amazon Social Distancing Outfit']
  Thakur    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Thakur Coronavirus']
  Chuck Norris    Hospital  ,['LOC'],['Chuck Norris Hospital']
  Covid19    Quarantine    Coronavirus    Eggs  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Toilet Paper    Christmas  ,[],[]
  Bank Balance    Friday  ,[],[]
  Chuck Norris    Coronavirus    Usa  ,['MISC'],['Chuck Norris Coronavirus Usa']
  Food    Waiter    Dog  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Coronavirus    Pornhub    Porn  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Chancellor Jones    President Tim Killeen        Covid19    Tim Killeen    Jones  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Chancellor Jones', 'Tim Killeen Covid19', 'Tim Killeen Jones']
  Dr  Anthony Fauci    Donald Trump    Mask  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Anthony Fauci', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  Grocery Shop  ,['ORG'],['Grocery Shop']
  Chinese Kid    People    Chinese Student    Everyone    Class    Other Students  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'Chinese']
  Social Distancing  ,[],[]
  Climate Change    Greta Thunberg    Coronavirus    Boris Johnson    Work From Home  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Climate Change', 'Greta', 'Thunberg', 'Coronavirus', 'Boris', 'Johnson']
  Coronavirus    Holiday Trip    Me    My Friends  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Holiday']
  Mask    Bank  ,['ORG'],['Mask Bank']
  Mobile Phone  ,[],[]
  Tom Hanks    Keanu Reeves    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Tom Hanks', 'Keanu Reeves', 'Coronavirus']
  Potato    Boss    Microsoft Teams  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Potato Boss', 'Microsoft']
  Extroverts    Quarantine    2020    Introverts  ,[],[]
  Wilson Wilson Jr    Wilson    Social Distancing  ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Wilson Wilson', 'Wilson']
  Commerative Jewellery  Tissue Pattern Earrings     Jewellery  ,[],[]
  Media    Saudi    Oil War    Stock Market    Stock Market Crash    Coronavirus    Face Time    Virtual Prom  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Saudi Oil War Stock Market', 'Market', 'Coronavirus']
  Millenials    Virus  ,['MISC'],['Millenials']
  Donald Trump    Hairdressers    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Donald Trump']
  Cat  ,['MISC'],['Cat']
  Covid19    Karens  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Karens']
  People    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Cough    Memes  ,[],[]
  Spouse  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    Costco Water  ,['MISC', 'ORG'],['Coronavirus', 'Costco']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Batman    Wuhan    Bat  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Batman', 'Wuhan Bat']
  Family    Isolation  ,[],[]
  Kids    Covid19    Quarantine  ,['ORG'],['Kids Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Coronavirus    Nbc News    Corona    Corona Beer  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Coronavirus Nbc News', 'Corona Corona Beer']
  Covid Vaccine  ,['ORG'],['Covid Vaccine']
  Cough Syrup    Arvind Kejriwal    Chai    Narendra Modi  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Cough', 'Arvind Kejriwal Chai', 'Narendra Modi']
  India    Covid19    Italy    Dolphins    British  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['India', 'Covid19', 'Italy', 'Dolphins', 'British']
  Toilet Paper    Girls  ,[],[]
  Media    Cattle    Coronavirus    American  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Media Cattle Coronavirus', 'American']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Google    Home    Millenials  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Google Home Millenials']
  Covid19 Palliative Warehouse    Osun    Lagos  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['Palliative Warehouse', 'Osun Lagos']
  Part Time Job  ,[],[]
  People    Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['ORG'],['Covid']
  Anri Vaxxers    Anti Vaxxer S Parents  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Anri Vaxxers', 'Anti Vaxxer S', 'Parents']
  Quarantine    Kids    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Quarantine Kids Covid19']
  Boomers    Mask    Lee Hsien Loong  ,['ORG'],['Boomers Mask Lee Hsien Loong']
  Unemployement    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Global Media    Seasonal Flu    Covid19  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Global Media', 'Flu']
  Stomach    Fruit Seed  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Restaurants    Covid    Bars    New York  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'LOC'],['Covid19', 'Covid Bars', 'New York']
  Corona Memes    Coronavirus    Indonesian    Indonesians  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Corona Memes Coronavirus', 'Indonesian Indonesians']
  Teachers  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Mumbai Indians  Mi     Ipl    Ipl Fans    Chennai Super Kings  Csk     Royal Challengers Bangalore  Rcb     Delhi Daredevils  Dd     Indian Premiere League    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Mumbai Indians Mi', 'Chennai Super Kings', 'Csk Royal Challengers Bangalore', 'Delhi Daredevils', 'Indian Premiere League', 'Coronavirus']
  Who    Covid19    Coronavirus    World Health Organisation    World Health Organization  Who   ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Coronavirus', 'World Health Organisation', 'World Health Organization Who']
  Coronavirus    Arshad Warsi  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Coronavirus', 'Arshad Warsi']
  Live Events  ,[],[]
  Xi Jinping    China    Journalists    Jounralists    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Wuhan    People    Journallists  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Xi Jinping', 'China', 'Coronavirus', 'Wuhan', 'Coronavirus', 'Wuhan']
  Toilet Paper    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Coworkers    Meetings    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Jason Mamoa  ,['PER'],['Jason Mamoa']
  2020  ,[],[]
  Government    Governments    Earth    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Earth Coronavirus']
  Alcohol    Coronavirus    Kids    Adults  ,['MISC'],['Alcohol Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus Publicist    Coronavirus    Climate Change  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus', 'Change']
  The Cure    Covid19    Genx  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['The Cure', 'Covid19']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Sanitizer    Toilet Paper    Pawn Stars  ,['ORG'],['Sanitizer']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Trumpsters    Maga Hats    Mask    American    Masks    United States Of America  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Maga Hats Mask American Masks', 'United States Of America']
  Elementary School Teachers    Cdc    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Teachers  ,['ORG'],['Centre For Disease Control']
  Covid Infected People    Sick People    Coronavirus Patients    Coronavirus    People  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Family    Groceries    Toilet Paper    Grocery  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Narendra Modi  ,['PER'],['Narendra Modi']
  Covid19    Breitling Watches  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Breitling Watches']
  Wish Com    Orders    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Wish Com', 'Coronavirus']
  Corona Memes    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Corona', 'Coronavirus']
  Native Americans    Foreigners    American  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Native Americans', 'American']
  Family    Isolation  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    People Born In March April    Quarantine    People Born In March  April  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Mask    Bank  ,['ORG'],['Mask Bank']
  Canada    American    Coronavirus Party  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['Canada', 'American Coronavirus Party']
  Covid Infected People    Normal Sick People    People With Coronavirus    Coronavirus    Normal People  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Cat  ,['MISC'],['Cat']
  Homeschool Teachers    Kids    Teachers    Common Core Math  ,['MISC'],['Common Core Math']
  Mask    People    Contact Avoidance    Hand Wash    Disinfectants    Other Preventive Measures    Coronavirus  ,[],[]
  Family    Isolation  ,[],[]
  Sheldon  ,['PER'],['Sheldon']
  Patrick Mahomes    Kansas City    Kansas    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Patrick Mahomes', 'Kansas', 'City Kansas', 'Coronavirus']
  Covidiots    Donald Trump    Mask    American    Masks  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Covidiots', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'American Masks']
  2020    Time Traveller    Time Traveler  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Time Traveller', 'Time Traveler']
  Coronavirus    Extroverts    Covid19    Introverts  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Covid19']
  Abs    Tacos    Cookies  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Abs', 'Tacos Cookies']
  Covid19    People  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Memes  ,[],[]
  Tentin Quarantino    Quentin Tarantino  ,['ORG', 'PER'],['Tentin Quarantino', 'Quentin Tarantino']
  John Morgan    Shortage Of Toilet Paper    American    Toilet Paper  ,['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG'],['John', 'Morgan', 'American Toilet Paper']
  Donald Trump    Coronavirus    Mask    American    Masks  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Coronavirus Mask', 'American Masks']
  Vladimir Putin    Donald Trump    Mask    American  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Vladimir Putin', 'Donald Trump', 'American']
  Apocalypse Outfit  ,['ORG'],['Apocalypse Outfit']
  Karens  ,['MISC'],['Karens']
  People With Chronic Illness  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Joe Biden    Donald Trump    Tara Reade    Social Distancing    Mask  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Donald Trump', 'Tara Reade']
  Coronavirus    Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    People  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  School    Kids  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Covid  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19', 'Covid']
  Dog    Covid19    Coronavirus    Dogs    People  ,['MISC'],['Dog']
  Shops    Food    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Justin Timberlake  ,['PER'],['Justin Timberlake']
  Donald Trump    Dr  Anthony Fauci    Covid19    Andrew Cuomo    Anthony Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Anthony Fauci', 'Covid19', 'Andrew Cuomo', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Quarantine    Cough  ,[],[]
  Dr  Anthony Fauci    Donald Trump    Coronavirus    Disinfectants  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Anthony Fauci', 'Donald Trump Coronavirus']
  Hand Sanitizer  ,[],[]
  Meme    China    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Meme China Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Family Of 6 Members    Austria    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Austria', 'Coronavirus']
  Alcohol    Coronavirus    Kids    Adults  ,['MISC'],['Alcohol Coronavirus']
  Kitten    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Kitten']
  Donald Trump    Democratic Party    Pornhub  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Democratic Party Pornhub']
  Hermione    Daniel Radcliffe    Coronavirus    Harry Potter    Emma Charlotte  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Hermione Daniel Radcliffe', 'Coronavirus', 'Harry Potter', 'Emma Charlotte']
  Uganda    Covid19    Covid20  ,['LOC'],['Uganda']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  People Complaining For Covid19 Quarantine    Mayor    Covid19    Quarantine    Jaws    Jaws Mayor    People Complaining About Covid 19 Quarantine    People  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Covid19', 'Jaws', 'Covid']
  Government  ,[],[]
  Throat  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Toilet Paper  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Guy Eating A Bat    China    Toilet Paper    Bat Soup  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Virus  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Mask Virus']
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Simpsons    The Simpsons    The Simpson S  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Simpsons The Simpsons The Simpson S']
  Mask    Norton Antivirus    Diy Mask  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Mask', 'Norton Antivirus', 'Diy Mask']
  Sunday    June    Quarantine    Qurantine  ,['MISC'],['Qurantine']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Stay At Home  ,[],[]
  Covid    China    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Covid China Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Hospital    Libtard  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Mexican    Corona Beer    Coronavirus    Corona  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Mexican Corona Beer Coronavirus', 'Corona']
  2020    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Horse People    Horse Shows    Sports  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Covid  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Covid']
  Teachers And Staff    Covid19    Kids    Teachers    Government Officials    Government Official    Schools  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Chlamydia  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Chlamydia']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Vladimir Putin    American        Donald Trump    Mask    Taliban    Taliban Fighters  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Vladimir Putin', 'American', 'Donald Trump', 'Taliban Taliban', 'Fighters']
  Bills    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Bills', 'Coronavirus']
  People    Contact Avoidance    Hand Wash    Disinfectants    Mask    Other Preventive Measures    Coronavirus  ,[],[]
  The Cure    Toilet Paper    Genx    Tissue Paper    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['The Cure']
  Jason    Coronavirus    Mask    Jason Voorhees    Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Jason Coronavirus', 'Jason Voorhees']
  Company    Covid19    Pandemic    Companies    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Press Conference    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Stay At Home    Covid19  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Zombies  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Quarantine    Halloween Costume    Halloween    Kid  ,[],[]
  Zoom    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Zoom Covid19']
  China    Soup    Bat Soup    Bat  ,['LOC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Soup', 'Bat', 'Bat']
  Officer    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Officer Coronavirus']
  Mask    Lettuce  ,[],[]
  Joe Biden    Mike Pence    Coronavirus    Democrats  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Joe Biden', 'Mike Pence', 'Coronavirus', 'Democrats']
  Stay At Home    Ticket    Coronavirus  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Toiletries    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Joe Biden']
  Nhl    National Hockey League  Nhl     Purell  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Nhl', 'National Hockey League', 'Nhl', 'Purell']
  Lockdown  ,[],[]
  Airlines    Flights    Health Authorities  ,[],[]
  Monkey  ,[],[]
  Laughter    Coronavirus    Scientists    Memes  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Coronavirus    Stay At Home    Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Centre For Disease Control', 'Home', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Anushka Sharma    Haircut    Virat Kohli  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Anushka Sharma', 'Virat Kohli']
  Vancoouver    Government    Vancouver    Lockdown  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Vancoouver', 'Vancouver']
  2Nd Wave Of Coronavirus    The World    World    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'World World Coronavirus']
  K L  Rahul    K L Rahul    K L Rahul    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['K', 'Rahul', 'Rahul', 'Rahul', 'Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Fiji  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['Covid19', 'Fiji']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Nursing School    School    Halloween    Pumpkin  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Nursing School', 'Halloween Pumpkin']
  Plague    China    Disease  ,['MISC'],['Plague China Disease']
  Pandemic    Coronavirus    Work From Home  ,['MISC'],['Pandemic Coronavirus']
  School    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['School Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Introverts    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus China Virus']
  Chuck Norris    Coronavirus    Quarantine  ,['MISC'],['Chuck Norris Coronavirus']
  Meme    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Meme Covid19']
  Coronavirus    Birthday Plan    Plans  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Vladimir Putin    Donald Trump    Mask    American  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Vladimir Putin', 'Donald Trump', 'American']
  Governor Andy Beshear    Kentucky    Andy Beshear    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Andy Beshear', 'Kentucky', 'Andy Beshear', 'Coronavirus']
  Teachers    Coronavirus    The World    Titanic  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Teachers', 'Coronavirus', 'The World Titanic']
  Barack Obama    Movie  ,['PER'],['Barack Obama']
  Mask    Joey  ,['PER'],['Joey']
  Donald Trump    Covid19  ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Human Consciousness    Government    Stoplights    Mask    Consciousness    Masks  ,[],[]
  Crude Oil    Covid19    Crude Oil Prices  ,[],[]
  Finland    New Zealand    Covid19    Belgium    Iceland    Germany    Denmark     Women    Denmark  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Finland', 'New Zealand', 'Belgium', 'Iceland', 'Germany', 'Denmark', 'Denmark']
  Literate People    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Uk    China    Italy    Coronavirus    France    Spain  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC'],['Uk', 'China', 'Italy', 'Coronavirus', 'France', 'Spain']
  Summer  ,[],[]
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Coronavirus    Covid  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid']
  Therapists    Architects    Architect    Architecture    Government    Work From Home    Therapist  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Government  ,['ORG'],['Coronavirus Government']
  Kid    Mum    Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    People  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    U S  Immigration And Customs Enforcement S  Ice     Mexicans    Ice Truck    Mexican Flag  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'U S Immigration And Customs Enforcement', 'S Ice Mexicans Ice Truck Mexican Flag']
  Charmin    Commerical  ,['PER'],['Charmin Commerical']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Cities    Coronavirus    Co2    Citizens  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Co2']
  Quarantine Snacks    Quarantine Snack  ,[],[]
  2020  ,[],[]
  Dog    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Dog Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Travel Blogger    Covid19    Covid  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Covid']
  Parents    House    Kids    School    Schools  ,['ORG'],['Parents House Kids']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Taxes  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Donald', 'Trump']
  Coronavirus    Traffic    Work From Home    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Mask    Cruise  ,['MISC'],['Mask Cruise']
  Students    Exams    Pandemic  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Covid19  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Covid19    Covid    Coronavirus    News  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Covid', 'Coronavirus News']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Adolf Hitler  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Adolf Hitler']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Dogs  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Who    China    Bruce Aylward  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'PER'],['Who', 'China', 'Bruce Aylward']
  Wuhan Coronavirus    English Sweating Sickness    Coronavirus    French Disease    Sapnish Influenza    African Sleeping Sickness  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Coronavirus', 'English Sweating', 'Coronavirus', 'French Disease', 'Sapnish Influenza', 'African Sleeping']
  No Time To Die  ,[],[]
  People    Normal People    Coronavirus    Lockdown    Gamers  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Millennials    Public Health    Millenials    Black Death    Spanish Flu  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Black Death', 'Spanish Flu']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Homeschool  ,[],[]
  Hair Salon    Dog Groomer  ,[],[]
  Lockdown    Rick Astley  ,['PER'],['Rick Astley']
  Health Care Workers    Healthcare Workers  ,[],[]
  School  ,[],[]
  Osama Bin Laden    Andrew Cuomo    New Yorkers    American Crisis    Pandemic    Covid19  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Osama Bin Laden', 'Andrew Cuomo', 'New Yorkers', 'American Crisis Pandemic Covid19']
  Mask    Bank  ,['ORG'],['Mask Bank']
  Donald Trump    Corona Beer    National Emergency    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Corona Beer National Emergency Coronavirus']
  2020    Marty  ,['PER'],['Marty']
  Bottoms    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Turkmenistan    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Turkmenistan', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Nhs    National Health Service  Nhs     Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'National Health Service', 'Covid']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Russian Covid19 Vaccine    Russian Vaccine    Doctor  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Russian Covid19', 'Russian']
  Wuhan Virus    China    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Corona Beer  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus', 'China Coronavirus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Corona Beer']
  Students    Class    Webcam  ,[],[]
  Memes    Work    Coronavirus    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Coworker    Human Resources    Ghetto    Hr    Grand Baby  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Ghetto', 'Hr Grand Baby']
  Zoom    Email  ,['ORG'],['Zoom']
  Covid Scan    Covid19    Work From Home  ,['ORG'],['Covid']
  Vladimir Putin    People Who Invented The Covid19 Vaccine    Vladimir Putin    Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Vladimir Putin', 'Covid19 Vaccine', 'Vladimir', 'Putin', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine    Coronavirus    Mink    Pharmacist    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid']
  Covid19    2020  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Isarelis    Jewish    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Isarelis Jewish Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Mr  Rogers    Rogers    Slippers    Sweaters  ,['ORG', 'PER', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Rogers', 'Rogers Slippers']
  Corona Beer    Corona  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Corona Beer', 'Corona']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Antivaxxers    Anti Vaxxers    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Vaxxers', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Barack Obama    Cnn    Media    Virus  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'Cnn Media Virus']
  Antivaxxers    Anti Vaxxer  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Antivaxxers', 'Anti Vaxxer']
  Quarantine    Wife  ,[],[]
  Mask    Michael Jackson  ,['PER'],['Michael Jackson']
  School    Unvaccinated Children    Peanut Butter  ,['MISC'],['Butter']
  Profs    Professors  ,[],[]
  Vladimir Putin    Covid19    Russia  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Vladimir Putin Covid19', 'Russia']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine    Coronavirus    Mink    Pharmacist    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid']
  Antivaxxers    Anti Vaxxer  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Antivaxxers', 'Anti Vaxxer']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Covid Vaccine    Indian Council Of Medical Research  Icmr     Icmr    Covaxin  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine', 'Indian Council Of Medical Research', 'Covaxin']
  Covid Vaccine    Coronavirus Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid Vaccine', 'Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Government    Houses  ,[],[]
  Corona Beer    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Corona Beer Coronavirus']
  Profs    Professors  ,[],[]
  Quarantine    Grand Children  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Mona Lisa  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Mona Lisa']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Xi Jinping    Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus    Wuhan Virus    Vladimir Putin    Wuhan Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Xi Jinping', 'Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus', 'Wuhan Virus', 'Vladimir Putin', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Face    Dog  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Face', 'Dog']
  Covid19    Instagram Thots    Instagram    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Instagram Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Russian Vaccine    Smirnoff  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Russian Vaccine', 'Smirnoff']
  Vladimir Putin    People Who Invented The Covid19 Vaccine    Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine    Covid Vaccine  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Vladimir Putin', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Travel    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Travel Coronavirus']
  Turkmenistan    Coronavirus  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Turkmenistan', 'Coronavirus']
  Scientists    Doctors    Virus  ,[],[]
  Chinese    China    Chinese Boy    Coronavirus    China Virus  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Chinese', 'China', 'Chinese Boy Coronavirus', 'China']
  Weed    Coronavirus    Scientists  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Migraine Patients    Coronavirus Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Antivaxxer    Anti Vaxxer    Anitvaxxers    Anti Vaxxers Parents  ,[],[]
  Wuhan Virus    Covid19    Feminism    Wuhan Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan Virus Covid19', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Vladimir Putin    The World    Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine    Salman Khan  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Vladimir Putin', 'World Coronavirus Vaccine', 'Salman Khan']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Vaccine']
  Donald Trump    Joe Biden    Mask    Covid19  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Joe Biden']
  Child    Power School    School  ,['ORG'],['Child Power School']
  Asians    Planet  ,['MISC'],['Asians Planet']
  Earth    Astronaut    Moon    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Earth', 'Astronaut Moon Coronavirus']
  2020  ,[],[]
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Governor    Bar    Bars    Coronavirus  ,['PER'],['Bar Bars']
  Maggie    Toilet Paper  ,['ORG'],['Maggie']
  Bar    Bars  ,[],[]
  2020    1820    1920  ,[],[]
  Jumanji    Coronavirus    Toilet Paper    Game Of Thrones  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Jumanji Coronavirus', 'Game Of Thrones']
  2020  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Centre For Disease Control', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Batman    Covid19  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Batman', 'Covid19']
  Memes    Bran    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Game Of Thrones    Wuhan    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Bran Coronavirus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Game Of Thrones', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Dogs    Humans    Muzzles  ,[],[]
  Xi Jinping    Wuhan Lab    Us State Department    Us State Deparment Communications    Wuhan    Wuhan Bio Terror Laboratory  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Xi Jinping', 'Wuhan Lab', 'Us State Department', 'Us State Deparment Communications', 'Wuhan Wuhan Bio Terror Laboratory']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Tmz  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Donald', 'Trump']
  People    Donald Trump    Mask    Masks  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Wuhan    Plane  ,['ORG'],['Wuhan Plane']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Mask Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Joe Biden    Mask    Masks  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Joe Biden']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Donald Trump    White House    Mask    Donald Trump    Republican  ,['PER', 'LOC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'White House', 'Donald Trump', 'Republican']
  Google  ,['ORG'],['Google']
  Parents    School    Teachers  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Jeans  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus Jeans']
  Quarantine    Roommate  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Xi Jinping    Impeachment    Wuhan    Virus  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Barack Obama', 'Xi Jinping', 'Wuhan Virus']
  Italy    Flight  ,['LOC'],['Italy']
  Work From Home    Dogs    Dog  ,[],[]
  Canada    Coronavirus    Face Mask Industry    Mask  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Canada', 'Coronavirus Face Mask Industry']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Mask Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Phd Students  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Jason Momoa  ,['PER'],['Jason Momoa']
  Wuhan Virus    China    Nsf    Wuhan Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Wuhan', 'Virus', 'China', 'Wuhan Coronavirus']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  China    Wuhan Virus    Wuhanpneumonia    Coronavirus    Wuhan Coronavirus    Bats    Bat  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['China', 'Wuhan Virus', 'Wuhanpneumonia Coronavirus', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Bats', 'Bat']
  Assignments    School    Professor    Canvas  ,[],[]
  Memes    Coronavrius Meme    Coronavirus    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavrius Meme', 'Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Coronavirus    Joe Biden    Mask  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Coronavirus', 'Joe Biden']
  Dogs    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Joe Biden    Donald Trump    Melania Trump    Twitter    Covid19    Melania    Covid  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Donald Trump', 'Melania Trump', 'Melania Covid']
  Greta Thunberg    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Greta Thunberg', 'Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Eminem    Greta Thunberg  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Eminem', 'Greta Thunberg']
  School    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['School Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Chinese    Bats    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Chinese Bats Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Chinese    Wuhan Virus    China    Wuhan Coronavirus    Wuhan    China Virus  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Chinese Wuhan Virus', 'China', 'Wuhan Coronavirus', 'Wuhan China']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Dr  Anthony Fauci    Donald Trump    Mask  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Anthony Fauci', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  Republican    Mask    Donald Trump  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Republican', 'Donald Trump']
  Introvert    Stay At Home    Society    Introverts  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Stay', 'At', 'Home Society']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Covid19  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Travel Agents  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Hillary Clinton    Spirit Halloween    Donald Trump    Halloween  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Hillary Clinton', 'Donald Trump']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Social Media    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Social Media Coronavirus']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Covid19    Sadler    Memes    Pandemic    Dr  Sadler  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Sadler Memes Pandemic', 'Sadler']
  Donald Trump    Nbc News    National Emergency  ,['PER', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Nbc News National Emergency']
  Trump Administration    China    Us Population    Donald Trump Administration    Donald Trump    Covid19    Pandemic  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Trump Administration', 'China', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'Pandemic']
  People All Over The World    2020  ,['MISC'],['World']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Covid19  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Donald Trump    The Legend Of Zelda  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'The Legend Of Zelda']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Experts    New Yorkers    Work From Home    Londoners  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['New Yorkers', 'Londoners']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Covid19    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19', 'Joe Biden']
  Donald Trump Suporters    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Donald Trump']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Japan  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Japan']
  Country    Hair Cuts  ,['MISC'],['Country']
  Houston Astros    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Houston Astros', 'Coronavirus']
  Asian    China    Asians    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Asian', 'China', 'Asians Coronavirus']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Mike Pence  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Mike Pence']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Family    Isolation  ,[],[]
  Gop    Coronavirus    Norton Antivirus    Coronavirus    Mask    Grand Old Party  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Gop Coronavirus', 'Norton Antivirus', 'Coronavirus Mask Grand Old Party']
  China    Usa    Plague    Area 51    Us    China  Us  ,['LOC', 'LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC'],['China', 'Usa Plague', 'Area', 'China']
  Mask    American Lives    Donald Trump  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Mask American Lives', 'Donald Trump']
  Fishing    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Fishing', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Wuhan    The World    Rest Of The World  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC'],['Wuhan', 'World', 'Rest Of', 'The World']
  Donald Trump    Halloween  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Donald', 'Trump']
  Dog    Dogs    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Dog Dogs Coronavirus']
  Chinese    Chinese Boy    Virus    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Chinese Chinese Boy Virus Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Medicine    Coronavirus    Soap    Virus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Introvert    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Introverts    Coronavirus    Extroverts    Mask    Masks    Hand Sanitizer    Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'ORG'],['Centre For Disease Control', 'Coronavirus', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Donald Trump    Pope    Coronavirus    Mask    Jesus Christ  ,['PER', 'PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Coronavirus', 'Mask', 'Jesus Christ']
  Las Vegas    Toilet Paper  ,['LOC'],['Las Vegas']
  Zoom Call    Zoom Meeting    Zoom  ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Zoom', 'Zoom', 'Zoom']
  Coronavirus    2020  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus 2020']
  Donald Trump    Ivanka Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Ivanka Trump']
  Donald Trump    Mask    People  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Friends    Lockdown    Grocery Store  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Friends Lockdown', 'Store']
  Kids  ,[],[]
  Covid Infected People    Fever Infected People    Coronavirus    Stay At Home    People With Normal Fever  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Adolf Hitler  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Adolf Hitler']
  Kids    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Kids Coronavirus']
  Liberals    Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER'],['Liberals', 'Donald Trump']
  Virus  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Club Team    Club Teams  ,['ORG'],['Coronavirus Club']
  Boss  ,['PER'],['Boss']
  Corona Beer    Coronavirus    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Corona Beer Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Grandpa    2020    Memes  ,[],[]
  Netflix  ,['ORG'],['Netflix']
  Monica  ,['PER'],['Monica']
  China  ,['LOC'],['China']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Lone Ranger  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Lone Ranger']
  Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Miami  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Miami']
  Easter    Lockdown    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Easter Lockdown Coronavirus']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Mandalorian  ,['MISC'],['Mandalorian']
  Mask    Chuck Norris  ,['PER'],['Chuck Norris']
  Donald Trump    Impeachment    Coronavirus  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Coronavirus']
  Bus Stop    Covid Marshalls  ,['ORG'],['Covid Marshalls']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Veterans Hospitals  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Donald Trump', 'Hospitals']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Democrats    Bandits    Democratic Party    2020    Mask  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump', 'Democrats Bandits', 'Democratic Party']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Mask    Pandemic    Covid19  ,['MISC'],['Mask Pandemic Covid19']
  Bigfoot    Social Distancing    Sasquatch  Bigfoot  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Bigfoot', 'Sasquatch', 'Bigfoot']
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Covid19    Flotus    Quarantine    Clorox    Jill Biden  ,['PER', 'PER', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama', 'Covid19', 'Flotus Quarantine', 'Clorox', 'Jill Biden']
  Uk    Covid19    Coronavirus Testing Kits    Coronavirus    Corona Testing  ,['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Uk', 'Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  2020    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Carole Baskin    Coronavirus    Joe Exotic    Netflix  ,['PER', 'ORG', 'PER', 'ORG'],['Carole Baskin', 'Coronavirus', 'Exotic', 'Netflix']
  Quarantine    Ration  ,[],[]
  Dogs    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Dogs', 'Coronavirus']
  Pub    Bars  ,[],[]
  Mask    Karens  ,['MISC'],['Karens']
  People    2020    Coronavirus    2019    Area 51    Virus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Area 51']
  Carolyn Goodman  Las Vagas Mayor     Las Vegas    Mayor  ,['PER', 'LOC'],['Carolyn Goodman Las Vagas', 'Las Vegas']
  Mask    Donald Trump    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Mask', 'Donald Trump Coronavirus']
  Dr  Fauci    Kathy Hochul    Mask    Dr  Anthony Fauci  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Fauci', 'Kathy Hochul', 'Anthony Fauci']
  Donald Trump    Democrats    Coronavirus    Mask    Qanon  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Democrats', 'Coronavirus Mask Qanon']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Covid19    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'Coronavirus']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Melania Trump    Mask  ,['PER'],['Melania Trump']
  Teacher    Teachers    Online Class  ,[],[]
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Goya  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Goya']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Work From Home  ,[],[]
  2020    Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Covid Marshalls  ,['ORG'],['Covid Marshalls']
  American    2020  ,['MISC'],['American 2020']
  Covid19    Antarctica  ,['ORG', 'LOC'],['Covid19', 'Antarctica']
  Coronavirus Vaccine    Vaccine    Coronavirus    Covid Vaccine  ,['MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus', 'Covid Vaccine']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Debbie    Home School    Kids  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Debbie', 'School']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Joe Biden    Donald Trump    Mask    Covid19    Covid  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'PER'],['Joe Biden', 'Donald', 'Trump']
  School    Coronavirus    Schools  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Hitler    Adolf Hitler  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Hitler', 'Adolf Hitler']
  Corona Beer    Lime    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Corona Beer Lime Coronavirus']
  China    Apple  ,['LOC', 'ORG'],['China', 'Apple']
  Climate Change    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Climate Change Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Covid19    Halloween  ,['MISC'],['Covid19']
  Karen    Cat    Mask    Karens  ,['MISC'],['Karen Cat Mask Karens']
  Goa    Pandemic    Coronavirus Memes  ,['LOC', 'MISC'],['Goa', 'Pandemic Coronavirus']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Mask    Earth    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Mask Earth Coronavirus']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Darth Vader    Mask    Social Distancing  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Darth', 'Vader', 'Mask']
  Traditional Pos Systems    Hr Managers    Human Resources    Covid19    Coworker  ,['ORG'],['Pos']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Social Distancing    Masks  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Mask    Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump Centre For Disease Control', 'Mask', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Front Line Workers    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Front Line Workers', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Macaulay Culkin    Mask    Donald Trump    Social Distancing  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Macaulay Culkin', 'Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Covid19    Doctors    Covid    Trump Adminisatration    Disinfectant    Hydroxychloroquine  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Trump']
  Hair Cut  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Cnn    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Cnn Coronavirus']
  Lifeguards    Government    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Students    Assignments    Google Classroom  ,['MISC'],['Google Classroom']
  Republican Figures    Donald Trump    Mask    Republican  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Republican', 'Donald Trump', 'Republican']
  2020  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  School    Parents    Parent  ,[],[]
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Coronavirus    Chlamydia  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Chlamydia']
  Lube    Hand Sanitizer    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Gains  ,[],[]
  Travel Influncers    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Jason Memoa    Jason Momoa  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Jason Memoa', 'Jason Momoa']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  2020  ,[],[]
  Mask    Donald Trump    2020  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Work From Home    Inbox  ,['ORG'],['Home']
  Donald Trump    Trump Supporters    Mask    Trump Supporter  ,['PER', 'MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Trump', 'Trump']
  Coronavirus    Coronavirus Conference    Covid19  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus Coronavirus Conference', 'Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Hair    Lockdown  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Lockdown']
  Kids    Coronavirus    Alcohol    Adults  ,[],[]
  Covid19    Corona Testing  ,['ORG', 'ORG'],['Covid19', 'Corona']
  Office    Work From Home  ,[],[]
  Mask    Donald Trump    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Mask', 'Donald Trump Coronavirus']
  Covid19  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  Donald Trump    Andy  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Andy']
  Mask  ,[],[]
  Weed    Cocaine    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Darwin Award  ,['MISC'],['Donald Trump Darwin Award']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Baby  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask Baby']
  Online Meeting  ,[],[]
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump']
  Coronavirus    Zombies  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Mask    Melania Trump  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Melania Trump']
  Coronavirus    Memes    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Coronavirus', 'Coronavirus']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  2020    Marty  ,['PER'],['Marty']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Covid Infected People    Normal Sick People    Normal People    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Covid', 'Coronavirus']
  Coronavirus    Homies    Sports    Graduation    Teacher    Friends    Prom  ,['ORG'],['Coronavirus Homies']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Covid19  ,['PER', 'MISC'],['Donald Trump', 'Covid19']
  Masakkali  ,['PER'],['Masakkali']
  Vaccine    Coronavirus    Virus    Experimental Vaccine  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Weed    India    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Weed India Coronavirus']
  Parents    Home School    School    Covid    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Parents', 'Covid Coronavirus']
  Chuck Norris    Coronavirus    Quarantine    Covid19    Coronavirus Memes  ,['MISC', 'MISC'],['Chuck Norris Coronavirus Quarantine', 'Covid19 Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Quarantine  ,[],[]
  School    Covid19    Schools  ,['ORG'],['Covid19']
  2020  ,[],[]
  Dogs    Humann    Dog  ,['MISC'],['Humann Dog']
  Covid19    North Korea    Coronavirus Patient    Coronavirus  ,['MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['Covid19', 'North Korea', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask  ,['MISC', 'PER', 'MISC'],['Donald', 'Trump', 'Mask']
  Barack Obama    Donald Trump    Joe Biden    Mask  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Barack Obama', 'Donald Trump', 'Joe Biden']
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Press    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama', 'Joe Biden']
  Toilet Paper  ,[],[]
  Mask    Donald Trump  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Right Wing  ,[],[]
  Quarantine Snacks    Quarantine  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Centre For Disease Control  Cdc     Mask    Centre Of Disease Control  Cdc   ,['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG'],['Donald Trump Centre For Disease Control', 'Mask', 'Centre Of Disease Control']
  Joe Biden  ,['PER'],['Joe Biden']
  Weed    Coronavirus  ,['MISC'],['Coronavirus']
  Gorcery Shop    Social Distancing  ,['ORG'],['Gorcery Shop']
  Italy    Flight  ,['LOC'],['Italy']
  Grandpa    2020    Memes  ,[],[]
  Donald Trump    Barack Obama    Joe Biden  ,['PER', 'PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Barack Obama', 'Joe Biden']
  United States    Native Americans    Canada    Usa  ,['LOC', 'MISC', 'LOC', 'MISC'],['United States', 'Native Americans', 'Canada', 'Usa']
  Jason Momoa  ,['PER'],['Jason Momoa']
  Jason Momoa  ,['PER'],['Jason Momoa']
  Covid    News    Coronavirus  ,['ORG', 'MISC'],['Covid News', 'Coronavirus']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Patriotism  ,['PER'],['Donald Trump']
  Donald Trump    Mask    Adolf Hitler  ,['PER', 'PER'],['Donald Trump', 'Adolf Hitler']
  The World    2020    1944  ,['MISC'],['The World 2020']
  Assignments    School    Professor    Canvas    Professors  ,[],[]
  Purell    2020    Ear Pods  ,['ORG'],['Purell']
